<dashboard>
  <label>FAQs</label>
  
  <row>
    <html>
      <h2>Frequently Asked Questions</h2>
      <ul>
        <li><a href="#q1">Started the client, but not seeing any logs. Why?</a></li>
        <li><a href="#q2">What does the client status "SFPkcs12 : Unable to get certificate" mean?</a></li>
        <li><a href="#q3">I have Splunk installed on Windows, why does the app not work?</a></li>
        <li><a href="#q4">How do I configure the app on a Universal Forwarded where there is no Splunk UI?</a></li>
      </ul>
    </html>
  </row>
  
  <row>
    <html>
      <a name="q1" /><h2>Started the client, but not seeing any logs. Why?</h2>
      <p>The eStreamer Summary dashboard will always keep you abreast of the eStreamer client
        status -- look there first to see if it's running or not. If any error or problem is
        indicated, click on the status or go to the <tt>Help > Client Status</tt> page to
        see more a more detailed status.</p>
      <p>Another worthwhile thing to do when first setting up the app is to ensure the verbose
        logging is enabled in Settings. This will write STDOUT and STDERR messages to a file
        (<tt>$APP_PATH/bin/estreamer_debug.log</tt>) for determining how the eStreamer client 
        may be failing.</p>
    </html>
  </row>
  
  <row>
    <html>
      <a name="q2" /><h2>What does the client status "SFPkcs12 : Unable to get certificate" mean?</h2>
      <p>If the eStreamer client status is presenting this error, it generally means that
        the certificate password is missing or incorrect.  Double-check the password in the
        app Settings to ensure it matches what was entered during certificate creation.</p>
    </html>
  </row>
  
  <row>
    <html>
      <a name="q3" /><h2>I have Splunk installed on Windows, why does the app not work?</h2>
      <p>At this point in time, the app is designed only to work on Unix platforms such as Linux.</p>
    </html>
  </row>
  
  <row>
    <html>
      <a name="q4" /><h2>How do I configure the app on a Universal Forwarded where there is no Splunk UI?</h2>
      <p>As of version 2.1.1, a shell script has been added to help configure the app from the
        command-line. The script is located in the app <tt>bin/</tt> directory and has the name
        <tt>config_nogui.sh</tt>. This script should even properly interpret the existing
        configuration and prompt for new values.</p>
      <p>The Splunk instance may need to be restarted after being configured.</p>
    </html>
  </row>
  
  <row>
    <html>
        <p>More coming!</p>
    </html>
  </row>
  
</dashboard>