<setup>
  <block title="Gigamon® Adaptive Response Application for Splunk" endpoint="admin/macros/" entity="gigamon_eula">
    <text><![CDATA[
<div style="text-align:justify; margin: 30px; line-height: 1.8em; font-size: 1.2em;">
<center><h2><b>End User License Agreement Supplemental Terms</b></h2></center>
<br></br>
<p>These Supplemental Terms (“<b>Supplemental Terms</b>”), along with Gigamon’s EULA (defined below), are a legal agreement between the
end-user customer of the Gigamon® Metadata Application for Splunk and/or the Gigamon® Adaptive Response Application for Splunk
(“<b>Customer</b>”) and Gigamon Inc. (“<b>Gigamon</b>”). Gigamon is willing to license the Gigamon Metadata Application for Splunk and/or the
Gigamon® Adaptive Response Application for Splunk (each an “<b>Application</b>”) to Customer upon the condition that it accepts and
complies with the terms contained in the EULA as modified by these Supplemental Terms (together with the EULA, the “<b>Agreement</b>”).
To the extent of any conflict between the terms of these Supplemental Terms and the EULA, the Supplemental Terms will apply to the
Application. Except as set forth in these Supplemental Terms, the terms of the EULA remain in full force and effect. Capitalized terms
not otherwise defined in these Supplemental Terms will have the meaning ascribed to them in the EULA.</p>
<p>Customer’s use, duplication, modification, installation, or access of the Application constitutes agreement with and acceptance of the
Agreement.</p>
<p>1. <b>Definitions</b>. For purposes of these Supplemental Terms:
<ol type="a"><li style="line-height: 2.0em;">“<b>EULA</b>” means the Gigamon End User License Agreement, as amended from time to time, currently located at:
<a href="https://www.gigamon.com/content/dam/resource-library/english/user---support-documentation/ms-end-user-licenseagreement-7040.pdf">
  https://www.gigamon.com/content/dam/resource-library/english/user---support-documentation/ms-end-user-licenseagreement-7040.pdf</a></li>
<li style="line-height: 2.0em;">“<b>Software</b>” will have the meaning ascribed to it in the EULA, but all references in the Agreement to “Software”
will be deemed to also include the Application, exclusive of any third party code.</li>
<li style="line-height: 2.0em;">All references in the Agreement to “<b>Products</b>” will be deemed to also include the Application.</li></ol></p>

<p>2. <b>License Grant</b>. In lieu of Sections 2(a) and 2(b) of the EULA, the following terms will apply to the Application. Subject to and
conditioned upon Customer’s compliance with the restrictions and terms set forth in the Agreement Gigamon hereby grants
Customer a non-exclusive, non-sublicensable, non-transferable, worldwide, Perpetual License to use the Application in object code
format for Customer’s internal business purposes only, solely with GigaVUE-FM software provided by Gigamon or an Approved
Source on Gigamon’s behalf, and solely with Gigamon Hardware, Certified White Box Hardware, or a Supported Virtualization
Environment, all in connection with the Splunk Enterprise.</p>

<p> 3. <b>Technical Support</b>. The provisions set forth in Section 6 (Technical Support, Limited Warranty) of the EULA do not apply to the
Application. For the avoidance of doubt, the Application is not eligible for Gigamon Software and Product Support Program.
However, Customers wishing to provide Feedback or to submit questions regarding support with respect to the Application may
contact Gigamon at <a href="mailto:apps@gigamon.com" target="_top">apps@gigamon.com</a>. Gigamon values its Customers and will use commercially
reasonable efforts to respond to such Feedback or questions, but does not undertake any obligation to do so. If Customer provides any feedback
to Gigamon concerning the functionality and performance of the Application (including identifying potential errors, enhancements, and
improvements) (“<b>Feedback</b>”), Customer hereby assigns to Gigamon all right, title, and interest in and to the Feedback. Gigamon
may use Feedback without any payment or restriction.</p>

<p>4. <b>Term and Termination</b>. The Supplemental Terms are effective as of the date of Customer’s first access to, or modification, use,
or installation of the Application (whichever occurs earliest) and remain in effect until Customer’s failure to comply with any term of
the Agreement. Customer may terminate the License Grant section of these Supplemental Terms at any time upon written notice to
Gigamon. Gigamon’s rights and Customer’s obligations under these Supplemental Terms survive the termination of the
Agreement. Upon termination of the Supplemental Terms and upon Gigamon’s request, Customer will certify in writing to Gigamon
that all instances and copies of the Application, or any portion thereof, have either been returned to Gigamon or otherwise
destroyed or deleted from any of its devices or storage devices.</p>

<p>5. <b>Miscellaneous</b>. These Supplemental Terms, along with the EULA, set forth the entire agreement between Customer and
Gigamon (the “<b>Parties</b>”) with respect to the subject matter set forth herein and supersedes any and all prior agreements or
understandings between the Parties about the specific subject matter of these Supplemental Terms. Except as expressly set forth
in these Supplemental Terms, the Agreement is unmodified and in full force and effect. These Supplemental Terms may not be
modified except by a written instrument duly executed by authorized representatives of the Parties and no course of dealing or
usage of trade may be invoked to modify these Supplemental Terms.</p>

</div>
]]>
    </text>
    <input field="definition">
      <label>I have read and understood the terms of this EULA</label>
      <type>bool</type>
    </input>
  <text><![CDATA[<h3>If you agree to the above terms click "Save" otherwise click "Cancel".</h3>]]></text>
</block>

</setup>

