<!--
### Copyright 2017 RTP Technology Inc. - Full details found here: $SPLUNK_HOME/etc/apps/Splunk_TA_RTP-Health-Checker/defaut/LICENSE.txt 
-->

<setup>
  <block title="RTP Technology Health Check Configuration" endpoint="admin/rtpHealthCheckerConf" entity="default">
   <text>Setup your health check here.  When you click save, you will be asked to restart Splunk.</text>
   <input field="company">
    <label>What is your company's name?</label>
    <type>string</type>
   </input>
   <input field="contact_first_name">
    <label>What is your first name?</label>
    <type>string</type>
   </input>
   <input field="contact_last_name">
    <label>What is your last name?</label>
    <type>string</type>
   </input>
   <input field="contact_email">
    <label>What is your email address?</label>
    <type>string</type>
   </input>
   <input field="contact_phone">
    <label>What is your phone number including extension if applicable?</label>
    <type>string</type>
   </input>
   <input field="admin_user">
    <label>Admin user that health searches will run as: *</label>
    <type>string</type>
   </input>
   <text>* This Splunk user needs access to internal indexes like _audit and _internal, also needs access to rest endpoints. THE USERNAME WILL NOT BE SENT TO RTP Technology.</text>
   <input field="send_capacity_data" >
    <label>I would like to send capacity data?</label>
    <type>bool</type>
   </input>
   <input field="send_general_data" >
    <label>I would like to send general data?</label>
    <type>bool</type>
   </input>
   <input field="send_health_data" >
    <label>I would like to send health data?</label>
    <type>bool</type>
   </input>
   <input field="no_internet" >
    <label>I do not have internet. **</label>
    <type>bool</type>
   </input>
   <text>** If this Splunk instance does not have internet access, please check this box.  This will create a package that can be emailed or otherwise provided to RTP Technology.  The package will be created in $SPLUNK_HOME/etc/apps/Splunk_TA_RTP-Health-Checker/lookups/RTPHealthCheckData.tar.gz
   </text>
   <input field="license_agreement" >
    <label>I agree to the license agreement. ***</label>
    <type>bool</type>
   </input>
   <text>*** By checking this box you agree to the full software license agreement found in the LICENSE file found here $SPLUNK_HOME/etc/apps/Splunk_TA_RTP-Health-Checker/defaut/LICENSE.txt</text>
   <text>*** PLEASE NOTE *** Sending your data to RTP Technology is a one time automated process that occurs when you select the items below, click save, AND then RESTART Splunk. The data that is sent might be sensitive to you or your organization, therefore you should review the searches in the reports tab before clicking save. By clicking save you agree to provide the data within those searches to RTP Technology via a secure API, which will be contacted from the Splunk instance you have installed this application on. If you have selected "I do not have internet" then you must manually send the data found here, $SPLUNK_HOME/etc/apps/Splunk_TA_RTP-Health-Checker/lookups/offline_package.tar.gz, to RTP Technology. You can send it to Splunk@RTPTech.com or call (201) 796-2266 and ask to speak with someone on the Splunk team for more options or any other questions you may have.</text>
  </block>
</setup>