<dashboard theme="light" version="1.1" hideEdit="true">
    <label>Welcome</label>
    <row>
        <panel>
            <html>
            <style>
                .images {
                    display: block;
                    margin: 1.5% auto 0 7%;
                    width: 725px;
                }
 
                .introduction h3,
                .configuration h3 {
                    font-size: 24px;
                    padding: 4px 0px;
                }
 
                .indent {
                    text-indent: 3em;
                }
 
                .configuration {
                    margin-left: 1.5%;
                }
 
                .dashboard-title {
                    display: none;
                }
 
                .first_section {
                    margin: 2% 0 13px 1.5%;
                }
 
                .avotrix_logo {
                    position: relative;
                    top: 45px;
                }
 
                .download {
                    background-color: #53a051;
                    color: #fff;
                    border-color: #53a051;
                }
            </style>
            <div>
                <div class="first_section">
                    <div class="avotrix_logo" style="float: right; display: inline-block; top: -9px; width: 35%;">
                        <img class="images" src="/static/app/bitbucket_addon_for_splunk/Avotrix_logo1.jpg"
                            style="width: 90%; margin: 1em 1em 1em 1em" />
                    </div>
                    <div class="introduction">
                        <h3>Welcome to Bitbucket Add-on for Splunk:</h3>
                        <p>The Bitbucket Add-on for Splunk integrates Bitbucket repository data into your Splunk
                            environment, enabling powerful monitoring and analysis of your development workflows. This
                            add-on utilizes the Bitbucket REST API to collect repository activities, code changes, pull
                            requests, and other version control metrics for enhanced visibility into your development
                            processes.
                        </p>
                        <p>Create an custom index on your own to ingest logs.</p>
 
                        <p>Get the Activation key by clicking <a href="https://avotrix.com/splunkapp.php"
                                target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="configuration">
                    <h3>Installation and Configuration:</h3>
                    <h2><b>Configuration</b></h2>
                    <p> To set up Bitbucket and fetch details, click on the button below and download
                        the manual. <br />
                        <a href="../../static/app/bitbucket_addon_for_splunk/Bitbucket Consumer Creation.pdf" type="button"
                            download="Bitbucket Consumer Creation.pdf">
                            <button class="download"> Download </button>
                        </a>
                    </p>
                    <p> To Configure the addon, click on the button below and download the manual. <br />
                        <a href="../../static/app/bitbucket_addon_for_splunk/Bitbucket Addon for Splunk Configuration.pdf"
                            type="button" download="Bitbucket Addon for Splunk Configuration.pdf">
                            <button class="download"> Download </button>
                        </a>
                        <br />
                    </p>
                    <p>
                    <h2><b>Inputs Details</b></h2>
                    <p><b>User: </b> Returns authenticated user info.</p>
                    <p><b>Projects: </b> Returns the list of projects in workspaces accessible by the authenticated user.</p>
                    <p><b>Workspace: </b> Returns a list of workspaces accessible by the authenticated user.</p>
                    <p><b>Repository: </b> Returns a list of repositories in workspaces accessible by the authenticated user</p>
                    <p><b>Commits: </b> Returns all commits in the repositories accessible by the authenticated user in topological order (newest commit first). All branches and tags are included (similar to git log --all).</p>
                    <p><b>Pull Requests: </b> Returns all pull requests state.</p>
                    <p><b>Pull Requests Activity: </b> list of the pull request's activity logs(OPEN, MERGED, or DECLINED).</p>
                    <p><b>Branch: </b> Returns the branches and tags in the repositories accessible by the authenticated user.</p>
                    <p><b>Repository User Permissions: </b> Returns a list of user permissions for the given repositories in workspaces accessible by the authenticated user.</p>
                    <p><b>Repository Group Permissions: </b> Returns a list of group permissions for the given repositories in workspaces accessible by the authenticated user.</p>
                    <p><b>Pipelines: </b> Return pipelines in repositories accessible by the authenticated user.</p>
                    <p><b>Workspace User Permissions: </b> Returns the list of members in a workspaces and their permission levels accessible by the authenticated user.</p>
                    <p><b>Project User Permissions: </b> Returns a list of user permissions for the given projects in workspaces accessible by the authenticated user.</p>
                    <p><b>Deployment: </b> Returns all deploy-keys belonging to repositories accessible by the authenticated user.</p>
                    <p><b>Project Group Permissions: </b> Returns a list of group permissions for the given projects in workspaces accessible by the authenticated user.</p>
                    <p><b>Workspace Webhooks : </b> Returns a list of webhooks installed on workspaces accessible by the authenticated user.</p>
                    <p><b>Repository Webhooks : </b> Returns a list of webhooks installed on repositories accessible by the authenticated user.</p>
                    <p><b>Audit Log : </b> Returns a list of audit log events for an organization.</p>
                    </p>
 
                    <p class="note">
                        <i><b>Note:</b> In a Distributed Environment install the add-on in the Heavy Forwarder
                            and Search Head. To avoid data duplication kindly configure the add-on only on Heavy
                            Forwarder for data collection. </i>
 
                    </p>
                    <h3>
                        Contact us:
                    </h3>
                    <p>
                        <b>Please feel free to reach out to us in case of any queries at support@avotrix.com.</b>
                    </p>
                </div>
            </div>
 
            </html>
        </panel>
    </row>
</dashboard>