
<setup>
  <block title="Welcome">
  	<text>Welcome to the DomainTools TA for Splunk setup page.
	  <![CDATA[<br>]]>Use this setup screen to configure DomainTools API credentials.</text>
  </block>

  <block title="Licensing Terms">
  	<text>
      This service is provided as-is, with all faults, as-available, and without a warranty of any kind.
      DomainTools may change or discontinue this pre-release service at any time without notice.
      Use of this pre-release service is subject to the <![CDATA[<a href="https://www.domaintools.com/company/terms-of-service/" target="_blank">]]>DomainTools Terms of Service<![CDATA[</a>]]>.
      Depending on the settings you select for this pre-release service, Splunk may charge you additional fees for your use of Splunk products.
      Splunk is wholly responsible for the pricing of its products and you should contact Splunk with any questions.
    </text>
  </block>

  <block title="API Credentials" endpoint="storage/passwords" entity="_new">
    <text>Please enter your API credentials below.</text>

    <input field="name">
      <label>DomainTools API Username</label>
      <type>text</type>
    </input>

    <input field="password">
      <label>API Key (password)</label>
      <type>password</type>
    </input>

  </block>

  <block title="Updating Your Credentials">
    <text>Procedure to Update DomainTools Credentials</text>
    <text>
        <![CDATA[<ol>]]>
          <![CDATA[<li>]]>Open a command line prompt on the Splunk server, logged in as a user that has edit access to the Splunk deployment.<![CDATA[</li>]]>
          <![CDATA[<li>]]>From the Splunk home directory, change directory to the local storage directory <![CDATA[<em>]]>./etc/apps/TA-domaintools/local/<![CDATA[</em></li>]]>
          <![CDATA[<li>]]>Remove <![CDATA[<em>]]>passwords.conf<![CDATA[</em>]]> and <![CDATA[<em>]]>app.conf<![CDATA[</em>]]> files.<![CDATA[</li>]]>
          <![CDATA[<li>]]>Restart the Splunk service.<![CDATA[</li>]]>
          <![CDATA[<li>]]>Enter your new credential information in <![CDATA[<a href="/manager/TA-domaintools/apps/local/TA-domaintools/setup?action=edit" target="_blank">]]>application setup<![CDATA[</a></li>]]>
          <![CDATA[<li>]]>Click Save<![CDATA[</li>]]>
        <![CDATA[</ol>]]>
    </text>
  </block>

  <block title="Important">
    <text>After submitting these credentials, please visit the <![CDATA[<em>]]>Settings - Application Settings<![CDATA[</em>]]> page to complete configuration options by confirming your custom search definition. The default search is:</text>
    <text>&lt;br/&gt;</text>
    <text>tstats summariesonly=true count(Web.url) FROM datamodel=Web BY Web.url | rename Web.url AS domain | fields domain</text>
    <text>&lt;br/&gt;</text>
    <text>If using a custom SPL base search, you must meet these criteria:</text>
    <text>&lt;br/&gt;</text>
    <text>1. If your custom base search does not begin with tstats you must add search to ensure proper functionality once it is merged into the DomainTools scheduled searches.</text>
    <text>2. Your custom search must not start with a pipe | character.</text>
    <text>3. Ensure the result contains a field named domain or use rename to create one.</text>
    <text>4. The search must efficiently return results from the last 10 minutes of events, ideally in a few seconds, but no longer than two or three minutes.</text>
    <text>&lt;br/&gt;</text>
    <text>For example:</text>
    <text>search index=mycustomindex | rename url AS domain</text>
    <text>&lt;br/&gt;</text>
    <text>Please also verify API connectivity from the “API Usage” section of Application Settings to ensure that your API username displays as well as highlighting in blue the enrich product associated with your API username. </text>
  </block>

</setup>
