<dashboard version="1.1" script="landing.js" hideEdit="true">
    <label>Event Builder For Splunk v2.0.1</label>

    <row>
        <panel>
            <html>

            <h1>Overview</h1>
            <p>
            Event Builder For Splunk is a security data simulation platform that enables SOC analysts and detection engineers to generate realistic synthetic log events across 42 sourcetypes and 21 security data domains.
            </p>
            <p>
            The desktop application sends events directly to Splunk via HTTP Event Collector (HEC), providing a real-time data stream for dashboard testing, detection rule validation, SOC training, and threat hunting exercises -- without requiring access to a live production environment.
            </p>
            <p>
            All configuration in this app is fully compatible with Splunk 9.x.
            </p>

            <hr/>
            <h1>Quick Start</h1>

            <ol>
            <li>Go to <strong><a href="setup_guide">Setup Guide</a></strong> to create a HEC Token and configure your connection.</li>
            <li>Open the <strong><a href="https://github.com/sooua/Event-Builder-For-Splunk" target="_blank">Event Builder For Splunk desktop application</a></strong>.</li>
            <li>Go to <strong>Settings &gt; Connection</strong> and enter your HEC URL and Token.</li>
            <li>Click <strong>Test Connection</strong> to verify the connection is working.</li>
            <li>Select your sourcetypes and click <strong>Start</strong> to begin generating events.</li>
            <li>Open the <strong><a href="live_monitor">Live Monitor</a></strong> dashboard to watch events arrive in real time.</li>
            </ol>

            <hr/>
            <h1>Key Features</h1>

            <h3>42-Sourcetype Event Simulation</h3>
            <p>
            Generate realistic synthetic events for 42 sourcetypes spanning Linux, Windows, Network, Web, DNS, VPN, Cloud (AWS / GCP / Azure / O365), IDS/IPS, Email, Identity (Okta), Database, Proxy, Kubernetes/Docker, EDR (CrowdStrike / Defender / SentinelOne), PAM (CyberArk / HashiCorp Vault), Monitoring, ITSM, and SaaS platforms.
            </p>

            <h3>Real-Time HEC Delivery</h3>
            <p>
            Deliver events directly to Splunk via HTTP Event Collector with configurable batch size, rate, and worker count. The <strong><a href="live_monitor">Live Monitor</a></strong> dashboard uses Splunk real-time search (rt mode) to display events within seconds of arrival, auto-refreshing every 10 seconds.
            </p>

            <h3>Pre-Built Security Dashboards</h3>
            <p>
            Five domain-specific dashboards providing visibility across all ingested data domains:
            </p>
            <ul>
            <li><strong><a href="overview">Overview</a></strong> -- Global event volume, EPS, per-index distribution (auto-refresh 30s)</li>
            <li><strong><a href="identity_access">Identity and Access</a></strong> -- Authentication failures, MFA events, VPN sessions, O365 operations</li>
            <li><strong><a href="network_infra">Network and Infrastructure</a></strong> -- Firewall allow/deny trends, DNS queries, proxy blocks</li>
            <li><strong><a href="endpoint_cloud">Endpoint and Cloud</a></strong> -- EDR detections, AWS/GCP IAM changes, Kubernetes audit events</li>
            <li><strong><a href="threat_detections">Threat Detections</a></strong> -- Suricata alerts, MITRE ATT&amp;CK coverage, high-risk entities</li>
            </ul>

            <h3>10 Correlation Rules</h3>
            <p>
            Preconfigured security detection rules, all disabled by default for safe deployment:
            </p>
            <ul>
            <li>Brute Force Login Detected</li>
            <li>Impossible Travel Detected</li>
            <li>MFA Bypass or Factor Deactivation</li>
            <li>Privileged Container Created in Kubernetes</li>
            <li>AWS IAM Privilege Escalation</li>
            <li>Lateral Movement via Pass-the-Hash</li>
            <li>C2 Beaconing Pattern Detected</li>
            <li>Data Exfiltration via Proxy</li>
            <li>Credential Dumping Tool Detected</li>
            <li>PAM Secret Accessed Outside Business Hours</li>
            </ul>

            <h3>21 Security Indexes</h3>
            <p>
            Purpose-built Splunk indexes for all major security data domains with 90-day data retention, using standard <code>$SPLUNK_DB</code> paths for AppInspect compliance.
            </p>

            <h3>Field Extractions for 42 Sourcetypes</h3>
            <p>
            Built-in <code>props.conf</code> field extraction rules covering all sourcetypes -- JSON auto-parsing (<code>KV_MODE=json</code>) for structured formats and regex-based extraction for syslog, CLF, KV, and vendor-specific log formats.
            </p>

            <hr/>
            <h1>Developer</h1>

            <p>
            This app is built and maintained by <a href="https://reallysec.com" target="_blank"><strong>Anhui Splunk Information Technology Co., Ltd.</strong></a>
            </p>

            </html>
        </panel>
    </row>
</dashboard>
