<!-- Copyright (C) 2022-2026 Sideview LLC.  All Rights Reserved. -->
<view stylesheet="custom.css" isVisible="False" >
  <label>Release Notes</label>
  <module name="TopNav" layoutPanel="appHeader" />
  <module name="AppNav" layoutPanel="appHeader" />

  <module name="HTML" layoutPanel="viewHeader">
    <param name="html"><![CDATA[
      <h1><a href="home">Home</a> / Release Notes</h1>
    ]]></param>
  </module>


  <module name="HTML" layoutPanel="resultsAreaLeft">
    <param name="html"><![CDATA[
<strong>Version 0.6.1 (June 9th, 2026)</strong>
<ul>
  <li>Another round of changes to improve our determination of which records comprise a single call. The previous changes in 0.6 had some problems, including one bug where all calls in a single coSpace were treated as a single massive call.</li>
  <li>Added the new key required by Splunk, "python.required" to restmap.conf.  No code change was required - the app was already compatible with Python 3.9.</li>
  <li>Fixed some Python 3.13 compatibility issues.</li>
</ul>

<strong>Version 0.6 (April 20th, 2026)</strong>
<ul>
  <li>Fixed a critical problem where our notion of "call id" and how the cisco_cdr app tied this together, was failing to merge sets of events from different servers into the overall call.</li>
</ul>

<strong>Version 0.5.4 (March 16th, 2026)</strong>
<ul>
  <li>Added a new panel to the CMS Call Detail page,  enumerating every value of every field in all of the call legs.</li>
  <li>First version of a more realistic landing page dashboard. Showing call concurrency,  top callingParty names, counts of calls vs encrypted calls, distinct deviceTypes and party numbers seen.</li>
</ul>

<strong>Version 0.5.3 (March 2nd, 2026)</strong>
<ul>
  <li>Improved the Call Detail page to also pull in events that don't have the call_id field but only have the callLegId field of one of the call's legs.</li>
  <li>Gave the Call Detail page a simple Gantt-chart style visualization of when each participant joined and left during the call.</li>
  <li>Fixed a bug on the Call Detail page where the table of call legs wasn't displaying them in time order.</li>
</ul>

<strong>Version 0.5.2 (February 9th, 2026)</strong>
<ul>
  <li>Fixed manager links in the nav.</li>
  <li>timestamps are now properly extracted.</li>
  <li>Improved the logic that groups together the disparate events that comprise a single call.</li>
  <li>Improvements to various field aliases and calculated fields.</li>
  <li>Added a view of the raw XML events to the call detail page, to make it easier to iteratively add/edit field extractions.</li>
</ul>

<strong>Version 0.5.1 (January 26th, 2026)</strong>
<ul>
  <li>Fixed some field extractions. Added new field aliases and definitions. </li>
</ul>

<strong>Version 0.5 (January 19th, 2026)</strong>
<ul>
  <li>First release</li>
</ul>
    ]]></param>
  </module>
</view>
