<!-- Copyright (C) 2022-2024 Sideview LLC.  All Rights Reserved. -->
<view stylesheet="custom.css" isVisible="False" >
  <label>Release Notes</label>
  <module name="TopNav" layoutPanel="appHeader" />
  <module name="AppNav" layoutPanel="appHeader" />

  <module name="HTML" layoutPanel="viewHeader">
    <param name="html"><![CDATA[
      <h1><a href="home">Home</a> / Release Notes</h1>
    ]]></param>
  </module>


  <module name="HTML" layoutPanel="resultsAreaLeft">
    <param name="html"><![CDATA[
<strong>Version 0.5.3 (June 9th, 2026)</strong>
<ul>
  <li>Added the new key required by Splunk, "python.required" to restmap.conf.  No code change was required - the app was already compatible with Python 3.9.</li>
  <li>App is now compatible with Python 3.13 as well as Python 3.9</li>
</ul>

<strong>Version 0.5.2 (April 20th, 2026)</strong>
<ul>
  <li>Fixed a bug that prevented the new homepage from working properly if the cisco_cdr app was not installed. (It would say only "Action Forbidden".)</li>
  <li>Fixed a problem in the app's health check that crosschecks indexes specified in the Cisco CDR app (if it's present) with the indexes specified in the SA's own "custom_index" macro.</li>
  <li>Fixed a bug in the drilldown for the "Top 20 Calling Parties" chart. Previously the drilldown clicks would take you to all calls to OR from the given number, not just the calls from it.</li>
</ul>

<strong>Version 0.5.1 (March 30th, 2026)</strong>
<ul>
  <li>Fixed two bugs in the drilldowns from the new homepage.</li>
  <li>Fixed a bug around health check messaging - even if no health checks actually failed the intro text for the messages would appear.</li>
</ul>

<strong>Version 0.5.0 (March 24th, 2026)</strong>
<ul>
  <li>This app is now marked visible by default in the list of apps, and it now has a landing page build in the Sideview UI displaying some out-of-the box charts such as max concurrency over time, top calling parties, and some summary statistics  NOTE: You must now also install Sideview's "Canary" app from Splunkbase.</li>
</ul>

<strong>Version 0.3 (February 24th, 2026)</strong>
<ul>
  <li>CRITICAL: The app no longer contains any index-time configuration, as this has been pulled out into the "TA_expressway_cdr" app aka "Supporting Add-on For Expressway CDR".  Consult the Sideview documentation and/or the README.txt of the two apps for further information.  Contact Sideview with any questions at all.</li>
</ul>

<strong>Version 0.2 (October 30th, 2025)</strong>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Functionality</strong> - IP addresses are now extracted from the 'details' field, as origIpAddr and destIpAddr.</li>
  <li><strong>Functionality</strong> - The App now has a custom detail_view, and "view call details" is available as new menu option for all calls.</li>

</ul>

<strong>Version 0.1 (October 21st, 2025)</strong>
<ul>
  <li>First release.</li>
</ul>
    ]]></param>
  </module>
</view>
