<!-- Copyright (C) 2010-2026 Sideview LLC.  All Rights Reserved. -->
<view isVisible="false" template="dashboard.html" stylesheet="update_lookup.css,custom.css" customJS="lib/custom_behaviors/tour.js">
  <label>In-Product Tour</label
>

  <module name="HTML" layoutPanel="viewHeader">
    <param name="html"><![CDATA[
      <br>
        <br>
    ]]></param>
  </module>

  <module name="URLLoader" layoutPanel="viewHeader">
    <param name="keepURLUpdated">True</param>
    <module name="Tabs" layoutPanel="panel_row1_col1">
      <param name="name">selectedTab</param>
      <param name="staticTabs">
        <list>
          <param name="label">Tutorials</param>
          <param name="value">static</param>
        </list>
        <list>
          <param name="label">Interactive Tour (Prototype)</param>
          <param name="value">dynamic</param>
        </list>

      </param>

      <module name="Switcher">
        <param name="selectedGroup">$selectedTab$</param>


        <pattern name="tutorial_topics">

          <module name="Switcher">
            <param name="selectedGroup">$staticTutorial$</param>



            <module name="HTML" group="call_investigation">
              <param name="customBehavior">openerLinks</param>
              <param name="html"><![CDATA[

                <ul class="tourList">
                  <li>First,  go to "Investigate > Calls" in the app navigation bar.

                  <li>You should see search results showing your most recent calls.
                  <li>Click on one of the values for 'callingPartyNumber'  or 'calledPartyNumber'
                  <li>In the menu that appears,  click "show calls to/from".
                  <li>Note that this added the extension or DN to one of the first fields on the page.  You can edit that textfield manually as well of course.
                  <li>Next click a value for a different field - perhaps 'cause_description'
                  <li>Note that you have options to either narrow down your search to only this value,  or to exclude this value from your results. Feel free to pick one of those options</li>
                  <li>NEXT - over on the right hand side of the page you'll see an "Edit Fields" button.  Click that.
                  <li>This layer is where you set what fields you want to see in the search results. In the top left of the layer note the 'filter' field.  Click into that field and type in the first few letters of a field - perhaps type <strong>qual</strong>

                  <li>Note that the available fields on the left hand side were filtered to only those that matched your filter.
                  <li>click a field on the left hand side that sounds interesting to you - eg <strong>quality</strong>.
                  <li>You will now see that field on the right hand side,  in the 'Selected Fields'.  Note that you can drag these selected fields up and down.   The vertical order there determines the horizontal order of the columns in your search results.

                  <li>click 'apply' to close the layer and re-run your search with the new field(s) you added and the new order.
                  <li>Next, we're going to manually type a searchterm.   In the 'search' field near the top,  type <strong>call_failed=1</strong> and hit return in that same field.
                  <li>If you get zero results,  try deleting the number you added to "calls to/from" and hitting return.

                  <li>OK you should now see only failed calls.

                  <li>Now we're going to briefly chart something we're interested in. Click any value of the "cause_description" field.

                  <li>A menu will appear.  Click the option in the menu that says "graph top values of cause_description over time"
                  <li>Now you have been switched over to the 'Chart' tab,  and several new form elements will have appeared.  Note that a form element that says "split by" has been set to "cause_description".   After the chart loads it will be showing you a column chart visualization of your failed calls over time.

                  <li>We'll come back to charting again in another tutorial. For now just click one of the bars in the column chart.

                  <li>In the menu that appears, click "Investigate these calls"

                  <li>It will have taken you right back into Investigate Calls. Note that your drilldown on the chart effectively zoomed in on that timerange, and that it also added a new searchterm matching the cause_description that you clicked on</li>
                  <li>Last but not least, click any value in the results and in the menu now pick the last option "view call details"

                  <li>This is the Call Detail page and it tries to present everything there is to know about this call. Note the 'Edit Fields' buttons in various panels. Also note that the top right hand panel allows you to exhaustively page through every value of every field.
                  <li>Note in the top left right under the navigation bar there is a breadcrumb link that takes you back to "Investigate Calls".  This will take you back to the filtered results you were just looking at.
                  <li>That's it!  You've completed the Call Investigation Tutorial

                </ul>

                Next try:  <a href="tour?staticTutorial=creating_charts">creating charts</a> | <a href="tour?staticTutorial=creating_dashboards">creating dashboards</a> | <a href="tour?staticTutorial=field_descriptions">learning which fields are available</a>
             ]]></param>
            </module>

            <module name="HTML" group="creating_charts">
              <param name="customBehavior">openerLinks</param>
              <param name="html"><![CDATA[

                <ul class="tourList">
                  <li>Begin by navigating to "Investigate > Calls" in the navigation bar.</li>

                  <li>Set a search filter or two that seems interesting,  or you can just type "call_failed=1" in the "search" field and hit return.

                  <li>Now click the "Chart" tab.  Many more form elements are available now but by default it'll start you with just a call volume report, meaning just the number of calls over time.
                  <li>Things to know -- first, you can always back out of Chart completely by clicking the "Calls" tab.</li>

                  <li>Second, you can always drill in deeper into your charted results by clicking elements in the chart and then clicking "investigate these calls".</li>

                  <li>For now though, note the pulldown that says "split by" and that is currently set to "(none)".  Change this from "(none)" to "cause_description".<br>
                  (One secret trick is to open the pulldown and type the first few letters of the field name.  This will jump your selection down to the right part of the list and you can use the arrow keys to get the rest of the way.)

                  <li>Now find the pulldown labeled "over" that is currently set to "time".  Change this from "time" to instead say "internal_device_type".

                  <li>You might prefer this as a bar chart - change the "chart type" pulldown from "column" to "bar".

                  <li>NOTE: If something in this chart is genuinely unexpected, click it and then select "investigate these calls"

                  <li>Next - go back to the "Calls" tab. We're going to look at some other ways to get over into charting.

                  <li>Click any value of any other field,  besides "cause_description".  Then pick the option that says 'graph top values for...'

                  <li>Nice work - you're all done here !

                    <!-- TODO - when we have a permalink button,  tell folks about it -->




                </ul>

                Next try:  <a href="tour?staticTutorial=creating_dashboards">creating dashboards</a> | <a href="tour?staticTutorial=field_descriptions">learning which fields are available</a>


             ]]></param>
            </module>

            <module name="HTML" group="creating_dashboards">
              <param name="customBehavior">openerLinks</param>
              <param name="html"><![CDATA[


                <ul class="tourList">
                  <li>If you have not already completed the "Call investigation" and Creating Charts" tutorials,  you might want to do those first, but it's just a suggestion.</li>

                  <li>You can return to "Investigate Calls", pick some calls and flip over to the 'Chart' tab,  OR you can click <a href="calls?searchterms=call_failed%3D1&type=incoming&stat=dc&yField=call_id&xField=_time&zField=cause_description&mode=chart&earliest=-24h%40h&latest=now" rel="opener">this link here</a> to jump right to a particular chart of <strong>failed calls over time by 'cause_description'</strong>.</li>


                  <li>OK. you may have noticed there is a button here labeled "Create Dashboard Panel".   Click it now.</li>
                  <li>select 'new dashboard'.</li>
                  <li>Give your new dashboard a name. Don't worry, dashboards begin life as "private" things that only you can see.</li>
                  <li>You can give it a title if you want, or leave it blank.</li>
                  <li>Submit the form.</li>

                  <li>Great job, you created your first dashboard.  Note the little blue link the messaging gives you - it would take you to your new dashboard in "Edit" mode, which we'll get into.  Don't click that yet.</li>
                  <li>Instead look up in the "Saved Dashboards" menu.  You'll see your new dashboard listed up there also.</li>

                  <li>Next lets make some change to the chart.  Change to a different "split by" option maybe, or change the timerange.
                    OR if you prefer, you <a href="calls?mode=chart&zField=type&xField=_time&yField=call_id&stat=dc&searchterms=call_failed%3D1&earliest=-24h%40h&latest=now"rel="opener">click this link</a> to jump right to a chart of <strong>failed calls split by 'type'</strong></li>

                  <li>Once you've got a second interesting chart, now click "Create Dashboard Panel" again.</li>

                  <li>This time, select "existing dashboard"</li>

                  <li>Select the name of the dashboard you created earlier and submit the form.</li>

                  <li>Now, finally, lets click the little blue link to go to our dashboard (or if you prefer, open "Saved Dashboards" and select it there)</li>

                  <li>If you followed the blue link,  the dashboard will be in "Edit mode" which is a little overwhelming because it has so many controls visible.  Click "Cancel" to return to the normal mode that normal users will see when they go to the dashboard.</li>

                  <li>You should see the  two charts that we threw over the wall.  Let's review some main points.
                    <ul>

                      <li><strong>Drilldown</strong> - If you create your panels from within the the Sideview UI,  drilldown will generally be live.  Try it and see - click one of the colored column segments.  It will take you to looking at those exact calls in the "Investigate Calls" page.</li>
                      <li><strong>Exporting a PDF</strong> - If you're out of Edit mode, note there is an "export" button in the top right.  Pick that and click "export PDF".   This sometimes isn't as good as simply taking a screenshot and sticking it in your PDF but it's quick.</li>
                      <li><strong>Scheduling PDF Delivery</strong> - Within the same "Export" menu,  there is an option for higher-tier users called "Scheduled PDF Delivery".  If you don't see it, don't worry it just means your user doesn't have this capability in Splunk.  If you want to change that, ask your Splunk admins for help (or ask Sideview for what specifically to ask your Splunk admins)</li>
                    </ul>
                  </li>
                  <li>Next lets click the "Edit" button to go back into that edit mode. Let's go over some basics of editing these dashboards.
                    <ul>
                      <li><strong>Reordering panels</strong> - First find the little dotted bar at the top of each panel - you can grab this with your mouse and drag it around to reposition the panels.  You can drag it so the two panels are alongside eachother in a single row,  or to reorder them.</li>
                      <li><strong>Editing searches manually</strong> - Next notice the little buttons on the right hand side.  The magnifying glass button allows you to edit the search: <strong>USE THIS SPARINGLY OR NOT AT ALL</strong>.  The problem with editing the SPL manually here is that it will come out of sync with the drilldown options that the panel was given at creation time.  It's often better to delete the panel, go back to the Sideview page you generated it from, tweak the pulldowns and generate a new panel.
                      <li><strong>Change Visualization</strong> - Next to the magnifying glass you'll see a little icon of a column chart.  You can click that to change what visualization you're using.  ie to change from column chart to bar chart, or to raw tabular results.  This doesn't change the data at all, only the presentation.
                      <li><strong>Change Settings for the Current Visualization</strong> - Now look for the little paintbrush icon.  This is also just a presentation thing, except that the options that show up will vary depending on what particular visualization your panel is set to.</li>
                    </ul>
                  </li>

                  <li>This is all called the Splunk "Simple XML" and it is a very powerful system and a deep topic.  You can read more about it in the <a href="https://docs.splunk.com/Documentation/Splunk/latest/Viz/Aboutthismanual" target="_blank">official Splunk docs</a>.</li>

                  <li>That's it!  You've completed this little Tutorial.</li>

                </ul>

                Next try:  <a href="tour?staticTutorial=field_descriptions">learning which fields are available</a> | <a href="tour?staticTutorial=sites">sites and locations</a>

              ]]></param>
            </module>


            <module name="HTML" group="field_descriptions">
              <param name="customBehavior">openerLinks</param>
              <param name="html"><![CDATA[

                <ul class="tourList">
                  <li>There are hundreds of fields available and it's a little overwhelming at first. Although you might recognize some from the raw CDR format itself, this app actually creates most of the fields available. Let's go over how to learn about the fields on the fly, when you need to.</li>
                  <li>First step, we'll return to the app landing page by clicking "Home" in the navigation bar.</li>
                  <li>Find the bottom right hand panel titled "Explore fields".   You can explore the form elements here to learn about particular categories of fields.</li>
                  <li>Note the "search" field there, and type in something like <strong>pattern</strong> to see the fields where that word appears in the docs.</li>
                  <li>Next - inline help.  Go to "Investigate Calls" in the navigation bar.</li>
                  <li>When the results load,  click any value of any field.  Note there is an option "learn more about the <name> field".  Click that.</li>
                  <li>This just gives you another way to access the same content from the "Explore fields" content on the home page.  However it can sometimes give you ideas in the moment, as to what to look at next.</li>
                  <li>Next - especially if you're one of the admins,  you should know that several important classes of fields come from distinct functionality areas that are represented in the "App Settings" menu in the navigation bar.  If you explore these pages they will tell you more and give you links back to our online documentation.</li>
                  <li>That's it!  You've completed this little Tutorial.</li>
                </ul>



                Next try:  <a href="tour?staticTutorial=sites">sites and locations</a> | <a href="tour?staticTutorial=call_investigation">call investigation</a> | <a href="tour?staticTutorial=creating_dashboards">creating dashboards</a>


             ]]></param>
            </module>






            <module name="HTML" group="sites">
              <param name="customBehavior">openerLinks</param>
              <param name="html"><![CDATA[

                <ul class="tourList">
                  <li>First,  go to "Investigate > Calls" in the app navigation bar.</li>
                  <li>We're going to talk about Sites and Locations, for both external and internal parties.   Let's start with outside parties.</li>
                  <li>Use the "Edit Fields" button to add the fields "callingPartyCountry", and if you're in the US or Canada,  "callingPartyState" and "callingPartyCity".</li>
                  <li>The app builds these field values by parsing the full outside numbers according to some simple rules. (NOTE: outside the US and Canada,  you should make sure that your cluster's locale code is correct in <a href="setup_clusters" rel="opener">App Settings - Edit Clusters and Locales</a>).</li>
                  <li>You can click these field values to search on them,  use them as the primary axis or as the "split by" axis of charts,  just as though they were present in the raw CDR data.</li>
                  <li>Next... lets touch on internal party locations.   Since these are generally not full DN's,  we generally can't get location by parsing the number (granted... if you have fully normalized all calling parties then it's quite possible that you can!).</li>
                  <li>Regardless, what the app does for internal party locations,  is it infers it from the endpoint IP addresses.  Admins of the app can enter a list of subnets, and map each of them to a "site" that you define.  These can be very coarse grained or very fine grained - it is up to you.   In the end you might have "indianapolis warehouse"  or "bixby street office, 4th floor", or just "Oakland".  Again... you can click these, search with them,  use them as fields in your reports and dashboards.</li>

                  <li>One more secret before we leave the "Investigate Calls" page - Click "Edit Fields" and add two fields, "from" and "to".</li>
                  <li>These fields try to take all the location field values available from both the Sites logic and the DN-parsing logic, and present one short location value like "Philadelphia, PA".</li>

                  <li>Next we are headed to a different page entirely.  In the "Investigate" menu in the navigation bar,  click "Sites".</li>
                  <li>This page presents rollup statistics about each of the "Sites" that you have defined in the "Sites Lookup"  (again, for more info see "App Settings > Define Sites").</li>
                  <li>Note that over on the right hand side this page has another "Edit Fields" button.  Click that to see what optional fields are available.</li>
                  <li>You can click any of the rows to get various options.  For now pick an interesting site and then choose "View site details".</li>
                  <li>This takes you one page deeper,  to a page displaying more details, tables and charts of data around that particular site.</li>
                  <li>Change the timerange, click around in the other tabs.</li>
                  <li>Note:
                    <ol>
                      <li>Many elements on the page have "Create Dashboard Panel" buttons on them, so that when you need to tell a visual story about a location in your infrastructure, you can use these charts and tables as your ingredients.</li>
                      <li>The chart elements are (almost) all interactive.   Click them when you want more detail, or just to check that its all real.</li>
                    </ol>
                </ul>

                Next try:  <a href="tour?staticTutorial=failed_calls">failed calls</a> | <a href="tour?staticTutorial=multileg_call_flow">complex call flow</a>



              ]]></param>
            </module>

            <module name="HTML" group="failed_calls">
              <param name="customBehavior">openerLinks</param>
              <param name="html"><![CDATA[

                <ul class="tourList">
                  <li>First, go to "Investigate > Calls" in the app navigation bar.</li>
                  <li>A primary field when you're looking into failed calls, is the "call_failed" field, which is either "1" or "0".</li>
                  <li>For now,  in the "search" box, just type in <strong>call_failed=1</strong> and hit return. (NOTE, If you don't see very many calls, try setting the timerange pulldown to a longer timerange.)</li>

                  <li>Note the values for the "cause_description" field in your search results.   Click any of the values in the table to bring up a menu.</li>
                  <li>click the menu option that says "Graph top values for cause_description over time".</li>

                  <li>First, no matter what chart you end up with here, you can always drill down.  If there is something drawing your attention on the chart or in the legend, just click it, then click "Investigate these calls".   Afterward you can always use your browser's back button to come back here.</li>

                  <!-- TODO when we have permalink,  add some permalink items here -->

                  <li>You can also add this chart to a dashboard in the app.  Click "Create Dashboard Panel", select "new dashboard".</li>
                  <li>For "dashboard name" type in something like <strong>failed calls test</strong> and submit.</li>
                  <li>Click "Saved Dashboards" in the navigation bar, and you'll see your new dashboard listed there.  Note this dashboard is private right now, meaning only you can see it.</li>
                  <li>These are "Simple XML" dashboards, which is a Splunk technology and a fairly deep topic in and of itself. More docs can be found <a href="https://docs.splunk.com/Documentation/Splunk/9.4.2/Viz/DashboardEditor" target="_blank">here</a>.</li>
                  <li>Now let's try something different.  Change the "over" pulldown from "time" to "internal_device_type".</li>
                  <li>You may again see something surprising in this chart.  You can always click to drill down.</li>
                  <li>Now try changing the "over" pulldown to "gateway".  again, if you see something off,  by all means click to drill down and look at the calls.</li>
                  <li>if you've set up the "Sites" lookup, try setting "over" to "site".</li>
                  <li>if you've set up the "Groups" lookup, try setting "over" to "group".</li>
                  <li>if you've set up the "Devices" lookups and there are a lot of hardphones, try setting "over" to "productName" to see the failures broken out by hardphone model.</li>
                  <li>Note you can click "Create Dashboard Panel" again, and pick "existing dashboard",  and add more panels to that same private dashboard we created earlier.</li>

                </ul>

                Next try:  <a href="tour?staticTutorial=multileg_call_flow">complex call flow</a> | <a href="tour?staticTutorial=creating_charts">creating charts</a> | <a href="tour?staticTutorial=creating_dashboards">creating dashboards</a>
             ]]></param>
            </module>




            <module name="HTML" group="multileg_call_flow">
              <param name="customBehavior">openerLinks</param>
              <param name="html"><![CDATA[

                <ul class="tourList">
                  <li>First,  go to "Investigate > Calls" in the app navigation bar.</li>
                  <li>We're going to look for some more complex call flow.  Find the textfield labeled 'search', type in <strong>legs&gt;1</strong> and hit return.</li>
                  <li>If you have any 'multileg' calls in your current timerange, you should get some search results there.  "legs" simply refers to the number of call legs that have generated CDR for the call.</li>
                  <li>You might also try searching for <strong>transfers&gt;0</strong> instead of <strong>legs&gt;1</strong>.  This specifically counts the legs that represent transfers.</li>
                  <li>Click any of the values in the results table's cells,  and in the menu that appears click "view call details".</li>
                  <li>With multileg calls, an extra panel appears in this view giving you a visualization of when each call leg began and ended in time.</li>
                  <li>Also... because multileg calls are generally far more complicated, the top right panel can be of particular interest.  Spend a moment using the pagination up there to page through every value of every field in all of the call's legs.</li>

                  <li>Next lets click the breadcrumb link to go back to "Investigate Calls" with the searchterms we had.</li>

                  <li>Now let's look at some special fields.  Click "Edit Fields" and add these fields:  "on_hook_party", "initialCalledPartyNumber" and "leg_type"
                    <ol>
                      <li>"on_hook_party" represents which party went on-hook to end the call.  In calls with one or more transfer it will only be defined on the last leg.  In conference calls and general multileg calls, there can be more than one.</li>

                      <li>"initialCalledPartyNumber" is one of quite a few fields the app creates that are prefixed "initial*". This particular one is the "calledPartyNumber" of the first call leg in the call - ie the initial leg.</li>

                      <li>"leg_type" is a whole world unto itself.  These are labels you can apply to call legs,  defined by a search expression.  Call legs that would match the given search expression,  get labeled with the leg_type's name.  Sideview ships a few out of the box,  but these are designed to be created by you,  with specific definitions like "handled_to_agent",  or "autoattendant"  or "linegroup_rollover".   To find out more,  click "settings" in the top right, then "Event types". Then in the "filter" box,  type <strong>leg_type</strong> and hit return.  This will show you the ones that we ship.   The only rule you have to follow, is that each call leg can only ever match one definition.</li>
                    </ol>
                  </li>
                  <li>You might, if you want to get really deep into the CDR weeds, go back to "Edit Fields" and also look at "finalCalledPartyPattern", "joinOnBehalfOf_description", "lastRedirectRedirectOnBehalfOf_description", "lastRedirectRedirect_description", "origCalledPartyRedirect_description", "mobilityFeature", "origCallTerminationOnBehalfOf_description" and "destCallTerminationOnBehalfOf_description".</li>

                  <li>want to go fishing for some calls to turn a colleague's hair white?  set the "type" pulldown to match only "incoming" calls.  Then search for <strong>transfers&gt;2 on_hook_party=caller leg_type="hung_up_at_voicemail" </strong>.  These are outside callers who were transferred three or more times and ended up hanging up  (If no calls are found, try removing the leg_type term. Sideview ships that as an example, but perhaps you dont use Unity as your VM handler).</li>

                </ul>

                Next try:  <a href="tour?staticTutorial=concurrency_and_utilization">concurrency_and_utilization</a> | <a href="tour?staticTutorial=call_investigation">call investigation</a>
             ]]></param>
            </module>


            <module name="HTML" group="concurrency_and_utilization">
              <param name="customBehavior">openerLinks</param>
              <param name="html"><![CDATA[

                <ul class="tourList">
                  <li>First, click "Chart" in the navigation bar, and then "Call concurrency/gateway utilization tool".</li>
                  <li>Let the page load, and change the timerange to "last 24 hours" or even "last 4 hours".</li>
                  <li>Use the "gateway" pulldown to select just a subset of your gateways and trunks.</li>
                  <li>Next open the "call types" pulldown. Here you can restrict this analysis to just inbound or outbound calls if you like.</li>
                  <li>Next change the "split by" pulldown to "(no split by)".  This will show you the total concurrency of all calls for the given subset of gateways and trunks.</li>
                  <li>And next change the "split by" pulldown to "device type". This will tell you how much of the concurrent circuit usage is from hardphones vs jabber and other endpoint types like that.</li>
                  <li>Note that there's a "Create Dashboard Panel" button here.   You can tweak this chart to just how you like it and then throw it onto a dashboard.</li>

                  <li>OK next we're going to leave this page entirely.  Go to "Investigate Calls" and search for "call_failed=0". Feel free to click another value or two in the results to narrow down or to exclude certain results.</li>
                  <li>Now flip to the "Chart" tab.</li>
                  <li>change "distinct count of" to "max".</li>
                  <li>The second pulldown will have changed itself from "calls" to "duration".  Now change it again yourself from "duration" to "concurrency".</li>
                  <li>Change "display as" from "Chart" to "Line".  It's a little strange to visualize concurrency in a column chart.</li>
                  <li>This is a little intimidating,  but technically from here you can chart he concurrency of *ANY* cohort of calls.</li>
                  <li>Making it crazier,  you can also set a "split by".  Change the "split by" pulldown to "gateway".</li>
                  <li>Or if you've set up the "Sites lookup",  to "site".     Or if you've set up the "Devices lookup", to "devicePool" or "productName".</li>

                </ul>

                Next try:  <a href="tour?staticTutorial=agent_user_huntgroups">agents, users and huntgroups</a> | <a href="tour?staticTutorial=call_volumes
">call volumes</a>
             ]]></param>
            </module>



            <module name="HTML" group="agent_user_huntgroups">
              <param name="customBehavior">openerLinks</param>
              <param name="html"><![CDATA[

                <ul class="tourList">
                  <li>Our first stops will be just to look at call statistics by party numbers. Don't worry - we'll get to agents and departments and huntgroups soon.</li>
                  <li>Navigate to "Investigate > Extensions", and let it load.  If it takes longer than you want to wait, set a shorter timerange and it will load much more quickly.</li>
                  <li>On the left hand side it is displaying every party number that the app sees on the "internal" side.  Then for each of these it displays various statistics.  Click the "Edit Fields" button over on the right hand side.</li>
                  <li>Note there are quite a lot of fields not currently selected.  Also note you can click the little "x" icons on the right hand side to remove fields from the results.</li>
                  <li>Change the fields if you like, and then click "Apply".</li>

                  <li>OK Next, let's look at the fields "name" and "group" in the table.  If they are all blankm, that's OK. It means nobody has set up the "Groups lookup" yet.    (If you're an admin or if you'd like to just learn more about how to set up the Groups lookup, navigate to "App Settings > Groups and extensions" in the app itself.  Or you can read the <a href="https://sideviewapps.com/documentation/cisco-cdr-reporting-analytics-administration-set-up-groups" target="_blank">setup docs on our site</a>)</li>

                  <li>Conversely if the "name" and "group" field DO have values populating them, that's great !  it means you or one of your colleagues have already done the work to populated the app's "Groups lookup", either nightly or manually.</li>

                  <li>Even better, if they are populated, that will also mean that the "group" and "subgroup" pulldowns at the top will also be loaded with options. open the "group" pulldown and select a subset of your groups/departments. Click away to close the pulldown and let the results load.</li>

                  <li>Now note the pulldown near the blue submit button that just says "options".  Open that, and select "include numbers with zero calls".  Let the results load again.</li>

                  <li>This will now be showing the exhaustive canonical list of all the numbers listed under that "group" or that department in your lookup,  and call stats. Even including numbers in that "group" that had no calls at all.    Remember these steps for later, for when a colleague asks you if you can send an automated PDF every week showing call stats for their team.  Yes you can!  just come back here, use "Edit Fields", pick just the few fields that manager needs,  set the 'groups' pulldown to the relevant staff, and then "create dashboard panel" and you're done.</li>

                  <li>OK there's still more.  Next let's sort. Find the column called 'calls' and click the column name to sort the table by that field.</li>

                  <li>You'll be looking at the extensions that have made or received the most total calls.  Click one that looks interesting.</li>

                  <li>After you click the row, you'll get a menu of two options - "investigate calls to/from this extension" and also "view extension details".  Choose "View extension details".</li>
                  <li>Since this page is only looking at a single party number, you can change the timerange to a significantly longer timerange an the page will still load in a reasonable time. Set it to "last 7 days" or "last 30 days".</li>

                  <li>Some things here are easy to miss!  First you can click bars and points in the two charts,  and summarized details will load in the panels below.</li>
                  <li>Also there is a ton of flexibility in the search fields.   type into the "Search filters" textfield,
                    <strong>incoming&gt;10 OR outgoing&gt;10</strong> and hit return.</li>

                  <li>If the "Sites lookup" is configured,  you can set a subset of your campuses or buildings in that pulldown.</li>

                  <li>OK let's leave this page, but in a fun way.  sort by "calls" so you're looking at the high volume extensions again,  pick an interesting one and click that row,  then "investigate calls to/from this extension".</li>

                  <li>You'll be back in "Investigate Calls",  but now click some other party number field.  Note there are options in the menu to "view extension detail" or "view outside party detail".    So you're never more than two clicks away from those party number detail pages, to get a deeper understanding of where it shows up.</li>

                  <li>Let's switch gears. Navigate to "Investigate Huntgroups".</li>

                  <li>The idea in the Huntgroups page is very similar to "Investigate Extensions", except of course that the left hand side is all your hunt pilots,  and the rollup stats concern the call flow that is involved with the relevant huntgroup calls.  otherwise it's very similar so you'll find it familiar.</li>



                </ul>

                Next try:  <a href="tour?staticTutorial=call_volumes">call volumes</a> | <a href="tour?staticTutorial=devices">devices and utilization</a>
             ]]></param>
            </module>



             <module name="HTML" group="call_volumes">
              <param name="customBehavior">openerLinks</param>
              <param name="html"><![CDATA[

                <ul class="tourList">
                  <li>Let's dive in at the deep end.  In the app navigation bar click "Chart > Create New Chart."</li>

                  <li>You can create a huge number of charts on this page but it starts with just a simple call volume report.</li>

                  <li>First, note that you can flip over to see the calls just by clicking the "calls" tab. Don't click it yet though.</li>

                  <li>Second, note the two pulldowns under the "Chart" tab that say "chart the &lt;distinct count of&gt;",  and "calls".  With these two set this way,  no matter what else we do we're going to get some kind of "call volume" report.</li>

                  <li>From there, there are two questions  1) what calls are we including in our report, and 2) What fields are we breaking it out by?</li>

                  <li>OK. Let's start with #1. This will boil down to what search terms you have <strong>above</strong> the "Calls / Chart" tabs.</li>

                  <li>If you've already taken the <a href="tour?selectedTab=call_investigation">call investigation tutorial</a>, feel free to pop over to 'calls', click some fields, add some filters,  whittle down to some interesting set of calls, then return to "Chart".</li>


                  <li>OK,  on to the second question - what kind of call volume report do we want?  Note the next two pulldowns --  there is one that says "over time" and the next one says "split by (none)".</li>

                  <li>Change the "over" pulldown to say "internal_device_type".</li>

                  <li>That was no fun. There were too many fields and you had to scroll forever.</li>

                  <li>It's OK. There is a better way. First use your browser's back button (or if you have a fancy mouse, the back button on your mouse).</li>

                  <li>Note the browser's back button correctly reset your "over" pulldown back to time.</li>

                  <li>Now open the "over" pulldown again but this time don't scroll.  Instead type, letter by letter,  "inter", and then carefully hit the down arrow once. You will find it has leaped you way down in the list and it has highlighted "internal_device_type" for you.  hit return.</li>

                  <li>Now the "X-axis" of our column chart is various internal device types - perhaps hardphones and jabber devices.   And the y-axis of course is still call counts.</li>
                  <li>let's change the X-axis again.  Let's change the "over" pulldown to "type".</li>
                  <li>Then change the "split by" pulldown to "internal_device_type".  Try and use the type-the-first-few-letters trick again.</li>
                  <li>Now you'll have a pretty different chart showing a breakdown of incoming/outgoing calls,  broken down by internal device type.</li>

                  <li>Next try changing "chart type" from "column" to "bar".</li>

                  <li>Click one of the bars just for fun.   No chart in this app ever needs to be a dead end.  There is (almost) always drilldown live if you need to see the raw calls with your own eyes.</li>

                  <li>This is just the beginning.  Assuming you have CMR data coming in, try "over &lt;time&gt;" and "split by &lt;quality&gt;"</li>

                  <li>Or If the "Sites lookup" is populated you can look at the field "site".  If the groups lookup is populated, look at "group".  If the "Devices Lookup" is in place, look at "devicePool" or "department" or "productName".</li>

                  <li>Don't forget there's a "Create Dashboard Panel" button there.  Fire a few interesting charts onto a new dashboard.</li>

                </ul>

                Next try:  <a href="tour?staticTutorial=devices">devices and utilization</a> | <a href="tour?staticTutorial=creating_charts">creating charts</a> | <a href="tour?staticTutorial=creating_charts">creating dashboards</a>
             ]]></param>
            </module>





             <module name="HTML" group="devices">
              <param name="customBehavior">openerLinks</param>
              <param name="html"><![CDATA[

                <ul class="tourList">

                  <li>We will certainly cover reporting on device utilization and some advanced topics,  but first lets cover the basics of just investigating devices in your call flow.   Go to "Investigate &gt; Calls" in the navigation bar.</li>

                  <li>By default the "origDeviceName" and "destDeviceName" fields are selected in the table. If they are not there, click "Edit Fields" and add them   (or take the <a href="tour?staticTutorial=call_investigation">call investigation</a> tutorial if you don't know what we're talking about).</li>

                  <li>Let's use "Edit Fields" to add a few more though.  Click "Edit Fields" and type "device" in the "filter" field of the Edit Fields layer.</li>

                  <li>Click "orig_device_type" and "dest_device_type" to add them.</li>

                  <li>If you have set up the "Devices" lookup, perhaps
                    <ul>
                      <li>type "product" instead of "device" in the filter field, and add the fields "origProductName" and "destProductName"  (these will hold things like the exact hardphone model)
                      <li>or type "user" in the filter field,a nd add "origUserName" and destUserName".
                    </ul>
                  </li>

                  <li>Click "Apply" to set these as the selected columns in your results.</li>

                  <li>Of course you can click on any of the values of these new fields and get a menu of options to search and filter and report.   Note first that you can click "learn more about the XXX field".   Click that.</li>

                  <li>Next click any interesting looking value of "origDeviceName" or "destDeviceName". And choose the "view device details" option.</li>

                  <li>Now you are on the Device Detail page.  There is a lot here!</li>

                  <li>First, you can click any column on the main column chart to quickly peek at those calls inline.</li>
                  <li>Secondly,  it's easy to miss that you have quite a few options to modify the chart shown here.  Try changing its "split by" pulldown from "extension/DN" to "cause_description" or to "quality".</li>

                  <li>Next, click to the "summary" tab.  This will show you the values of every field having to do with devices. If you don't have the "Devices lookup" configured,  quite a few will be blank and that's OK.</li>

                  <li>OK next let's click to "Investigate > Devices" in the app navigation bar.  Or you can click the breadcrumb link in the top left of the Device Detail page -- the link that says "Devices".</li>

                  <li>This page will load and give you a table of devices and associated statistics.  Click "Edit Fields" over on the right hand side.</li>

                  <li>As always, there are far more fields available than what it shows by default.  You don't need to change anything, just remember that there are more fields hidden there.</li>

                  <li>Click the column header for "calls" to sort by calls, descending.</li>

                  <li>Now note the "device types" pulldown at the top, and set a subset of devices that seems potentially interesting.</li>

                  <li>Next, if you have configured the "Devices lookup", click the "options" pulldown and make sure "include devices with zero calls" is checked.</li>

                  <li>With the "Devices lookup" in place, and that checkbox selected,  this page becomes a very powerful tool to find and deprovision unused phones.</li>

                  <li>Into the "search filters" box type <strong>calls=0 OR (calls&lt;5 outgoing=0)</strong>.  The intention here is to find not just phones that are totally unused,  but ones that might be only barely used.</li>

                  <li>Note that you can set a subset of clusters and,  if you've set up the "Sites lookup",  physical sites and locations. One Note:  if you use the sites pulldown you'll want to deselect that "include devices with zero calls" checkbox.  It will give you a warning saying the same thing though.</li>

                  <li>Next we'll end with something simple.  Click any row in the table to bring up a menu with two options:  "investigate calls to/from this device"  and "view device details".   The device details page we've seen already so pick the first one -- "Investigate calls to/from this device."</li>

                  <li>Now you're back looking at calls again and you've finished this little tutorial.</li>
                </ul>


                  Next try: <a href="tour?staticTutorial=call_investigation">call investigation</a> |
                  <a href="tour?staticTutorial=field_descriptions">learning which fields are available</a> |
                  <a href="tour?staticTutorial=concurrency_and_utilization">concurrency and utilization</a>


              ]]></param>
            </module>



          </module>
        </pattern>



        <module name="HTML" group="dynamic">
          <param name="customBehavior">tourOrchestrator</param>
          <param name="html"><![CDATA[

            <ul class="tourList" id="dynamicTourList">
              <li class="selected">
                We're going to take you on a quick guided tour of this app.<br>
                <br>
                Whether or not this is your cup of tea, <a href="mailto:product@sideviewapps.com">we'd love to hear your thoughts</a>!
                <br>
                When you're ready, take a moment to position this window alongside the main window from which you launched this popup window, so you can see them both at the same time.<br>
                <br>
                Then just navigate to "Investigate > Calls" in the app navigation bar.

              </li>

            </ul>



          ]]></param>
        </module>
      </module>
    </module>
  </module>





</view>
