<dashboard version="1.1" hideEdit="true">
  <label>Monitoring of Java Virtual Machines with JMX v3.2.8</label>
<row>
<html>
  <h1>Overview</h1>
  <p>
  The Python code in this App is dual 2.7/3 compatible.<br/>
  This version of the App enforces Python 3 for execution of the modular input script when running on Splunk 8+ in order to satisfy Splunkbase AppInspect requirements.<br/>
  If running this App on Splunk versions prior to 8 , then Python 2.7 will get executed.
<br/><br/>
  This app provides the means to :
<ul>
<li>connect to any local or remote JVM's JMX server, either via the remote JMX interface,attaching to a local JVM process or using an MX4J HTTP based connector.</li>
<li>query any MBean running on that server</li>
<li>extract any MBean attributes (simple, composite or tabular)</li>
<li>invoke MBean operations</li>
<li>listen for MBean notifications and declare custom notification filters</li>
<li>write attributes and operation results out in a default key/value format, or plugin your own custom format, for SPLUNK indexing and searching</li>
<li>declare clusters of JVM's for large scale JVM deployments</li>
<li>manage the JMX Modular Input programmatically via the REST API</li>

</ul>
<br/><br/>
Tested to date against Hotspot ,JRockit and IBM J9 JVM's.
<br/><br/>
Currently supports the following  JMX Connectors :
 <ul>
<li>rmi  (JSR160 Standard Implementation and MX4J's JSR160 Implementation)</li>
<li>iiop (JSR160 Standard Implementation and MX4J's JSR160 Implementation)</li>
<li>local (MX4J only)</li>
<li>soap (MX4J only)</li>
<li>hessian (MX4J only)</li>
<li>burlap (MX4J only)</li>
</ul>

</p>

  <hr/>
  <h1>Quickstart</h1>
       
           <p>Browse to the <a href="../../../en-US/app/SPLUNK4JMX/activation_key" target="_blank">Activation Key</a> menu tab and enter your activation key.</p>
            <p>Browse to the <a href="../../../en-US/app/SPLUNK4JMX/setup_page" target="_blank">Setup Credentials</a> menu tab and enter any JMX usernames/passwords you require.</p>
            <p>Encrypted credentials are saved to <code>$SPLUNK_HOME/etc/apps/SPLUNK4JMX/local/passwords.conf</code></p>
            <p>Browse to the <a href="../../../en-US/manager/SPLUNK4JMX/data/inputs/jmx" target="_blank">Data Inputs</a> tab and setup your JMX Inputs.</p>
            <p>Out the box this app contains an <a href="../../manager/SPLUNK4JMX/data/inputs/jmx">example JMX modular input</a>. Before you enable this input , you should first edit the example 
    configuration file at <b>SPLUNK_HOME/etc/apps/SPLUNK4JMX/bin/config/config.xml</b> to point to your target JVM. Also be sure that your target JVM is correctly setup to expose it's JMX Agent.</p>           
            <hr/>

<h1>Search the incoming data</h1>

  <p> Once you have a basic setup configured and enabled, you can then <a href="../../app/search/search?q=search%20index%3Dmain%20sourcetype%3Djmx">search</a> your JMX data.With data now coming in , the example dashboards should start populating with data.Just browse to them via the Navigation bar above.</p> 

<hr/>


<h1>Developer</h1>

<p>

  This App is built and supported by the team at <a href="https://www.baboonbones.com" target="_blank">BaboonBones</a>

</p>
    
</html>   
</row>

</dashboard>