<view autoCancelInterval="90" isVisible="true" onunloadCancelJobs="true" template="dashboard.html">
  <label>Other tuning tools</label>
  <module name="AccountBar" layoutPanel="appHeader" />
  <module name="FeedbackLinks" layoutPanel="viewHeader">
    <param name="section">discover</param>
  </module>
  <module name="BreadCrumb" layoutPanel="viewHeader">
    <param name="options">
      <list>
        <param name="label">Home</param>
        <param name="view">home</param>
      </list>
      <list>
        <param name="label">Other tuning tools</param>
      </list>
    </param>
  </module>


  <module name="StaticContentSample" layoutPanel="panel_row2_col1">
    <param name="text"><![CDATA[
    'Tuners' analyze your configurations as well as how you've been using Splunk.  Then they suggest better ways to use or organize the search-time knowledge objects you already have. 
     ]]></param>
  </module>

  <module name="StaticContentSample" layoutPanel="panel_row2_col1">
    <param name="text"><![CDATA[
    <ul>
      <li>
        <h3>Tune event types</h3>
        <p>looks at the saved searches you've created as well as all the searches you've been running, and recommends commonly used searches as new eventtypes.</p>
          
        <!-- <p><a href="tune_eventtypes_1">(included in the app)</a></p>

        -->
      </li>

      <li>
        <h3>Tune lookups</h3>
        <ol>
          <li>finds very long "foo OR bar OR baz" searches, in either audit.log or savedsearches.conf or view config.</li>
          <li>find joins in saved searches and in audit.log</li>
        </ol>

      </li>
      <li>
        <h3>recommending macros</h3>
        <ol>
          <li>Find long searches that have substrings that are always the same except for one or two variables</li>
          <li>Find long searches that have substrings that are identical.
        </ol>
      </li>
      <li>
        <h3>finding unused saved searches</h3>
        <ol>
          <li>show the top 10 sets of similar searches run as ad-hoc searches</li>
          <li>top 10 similar searches that exist as saved searches</li>
        </ol>
      </li>
      <li>
        <h3>finding unused macros / who is using this macro</h3>
        
      </li>
      <li>
        <h3>finding unused eventtypes / who is using this eventtype</h3>
        
      </li>
      <li>
        <h3>finding unused views / who is using this view</h3>
        
      </li>
      <li>
        <h3>validate data inputs by host.</h3>
        <p>
          
        </p>
      </li>
      <li>
        <h3>Tune - find excessive REX usage -- suggest as fields</h3>
        <p>
          if the same rex commands are getting used by more than one user or in more than one view, we can suggest that this be extracted as a field.  We can even infer a good field name. 
        </p>
      </li>
      <li>
        <h3>Tune - find redundant searches in config/activity</h3>
        <p>
          If two or more users or two or more views views are using the same search we can recommend this as a saved search, and we can recommend whether or not it should be shared with other users or roles. 
        </p>
      </li>
      <li>
        <h3>Tune - running event-less reports in flashtimeline</h3>
        <p>
          If a lot of reporting commands are being run in the main search view (flashtimeline), those reports will be running quite a lot slower than they would be if run in another view like the 'advanced charting view'.  We can make a recommendation and show which users and views are involved.
        </p>
      </li>
      <li>
        <h3>Tune - analyzing date-time extraction</h3>
        <ol>
          <li>find sourcetypes that show events clumped in a single second</li>
          <li>find sourcetypes that show lots of large gaps in time with no small gaps in time</li>
          <li>find sourcetypes that seem to have indexed the same events 2 or more times.</li>
        </ol>
      </li>
      <li>
        <h3>Tune - analyzing multiline event indexing</h3>

        <ol>
          <li>our mining code thinks its single line but it's currently set to a sourcetype such that it's getting aggregated.</li>
          <li>our mining code thinks its multi-line but it's currently set to a sourcetype such that it's all single line data.</li>
          <li>we run mvsplit on "\n" to break the events into single line events. We calculate what the punct values would be.  We see to what degree those punct values also turn up in other single line events.</li>
        </p>

      </li>
    </ul>


    ]]></param>
  </module>

  <module name="ServerSideInclude" layoutPanel="panel_row3_col1">
    <param name="src">text/feedback_validate.html</param>
  </module>

  
</view>
