<dashboard theme="light" version="1.1" hideEdit="true">
  <label>Welcome</label>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
        <style>
          .images {
            display: block;
            margin: 1.5% auto 0 7%;
            width: 725px;
          }
          .introduction h3, .configuration h3 {
            font-size: 24px;
            padding: 4px 0px;
          }
          .indent { text-indent: 3em; }
          .configuration { margin-left: 1.5%; }
          .dashboard-title { display: none; }
          .first_section { margin: 2% 0 13px 1.5%; }
          .avotrix_logo {
            position: relative;
            top: 45px;
          }
          .download {
            background-color: #53a051;
            color: #fff;
            border-color: #53a051;
          }
        </style>

        <div>
          <div class="first_section">
            <div class="avotrix_logo" style="float: right; display: inline-block; top: -9px; width: 35%;">
              <img class="images" src="/static/app/ransomware_addon_for_splunk/Avotrix_logo1.jpg"
                   style="width: 90%; margin: 1em 1em 1em 1em" />
            </div>

            <div class="introduction">
              <h3>Welcome to Ransomware Add-on:</h3>
              <p>
                The Ransomware Add-on for Splunk collects real-time ransomware data, providing visibility into active threats,
                victim details, and group activities to strengthen ransomware detection and threat intelligence.
              </p>
              <p>
                Get the Activation key by clicking
                <a href="https://avotrix.com/splunkapp.php" target="_blank">here</a>.
              </p>
            </div>
          </div>

          <div class="configuration">
            <h3>Installation and Configuration:</h3>
            <h2><b>Configuration</b></h2>

            <p>
              To set up Ransomware account to fetch Token, click on the button below and download the manual. <br />
              <a href="../../static/app/ransomware_addon_for_splunk/setup.pdf" type="button"
                 download="How to Setup Ransomware Addon.pdf">
                <button class="download">Download</button>
              </a>
            </p>

            <p>
              To configure the addon, click on the button below and download the manual. <br />
              <a href="../../static/app/ransomware_addon_for_splunk/configure.pdf" type="button"
                 download="How to Configure Ransomware Addon.pdf">
                <button class="download">Download</button>
              </a>
            </p>

            <h2><b>Inputs Details</b></h2>
            <p><b>Csirt:</b> Collects information on ransomware-related CSIRT (Computer Security Incident Response Team) reports and responses.</p>
            <p><b>Group Details:</b> Gathers detailed profiles of active ransomware groups, including aliases and activity summaries.</p>
            <p><b>Listsectors:</b> Lists targeted industry sectors affected by current ransomware campaigns.</p>
            <p><b>Group Iocs:</b> Fetches indicators of compromise (IOCs) linked to ransomware groups for threat correlation.</p>
            <p><b>Negotiation:</b> Captures data on ransom negotiations and communication patterns between attackers and victims.</p>
            <p><b>Press All:</b> Retrieves press releases and public reports about ransomware incidents and group activity.</p>
            <p><b>Ransomnotes:</b> Collects samples and details of ransom notes used in recent attacks.</p>
            <p><b>Ransomstats:</b> Provides statistical insights on ransomware incidents, including group counts and victim trends.</p>
            <p><b>Victim:</b> Gathers details of organizations targeted or compromised by ransomware operations.</p>
            <p><b>Yara:</b> Fetches YARA rules associated with ransomware detection for threat hunting.</p>

            <h3>Contact Us</h3>
            <p><b>Please feel free to reach out to us in case of any queries at support@avotrix.com.</b></p>
          </div>
        </div>
      </html>
    </panel>
  </row>
</dashboard>
