<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<dashboard>
  <label>About Exponant</label>
  <row>
<html>
<h2>About this App</h2>

<p>Remotely monitor and troubleshoot Websense Web Security Suite (WSS). This app only supports version 7.7. Functionality includes traffic, user and security monitoring, as well as realtime filtering debugging.</p>

<p>Please provide feedback, submit issues and feature requests on Trello at:  https://trello.com/c/R9iViFQD</p>

<h2>About Exponant</h2>

<p>Exponant offers Splunk Professional Services worldwide:</p>

<ul>
<li><p>Implementation and Management of Splunk for Large Customers.</p></li>
<li><p>Splunk App development.</p></li>
<li><p>Custom development of Splunk collectors to assist in Data Acquisition.</p></li>
</ul>

<h2>More about us</h2>

<p>Exponªnt (Pty) Ltd., which was originally founded in 1998, was created out of the successful management buyout of Brainware Consulting in August 2000, under the leadership of its CEO Marius Pels. It is a software, services and consulting company with a turnover of more than R120m and comprising some 300 staff.</p>

<p>Exponªnt ISS is the division of the parent company, under the management of Wolfgang Selzer, Executive Manager, which specifically focuses on monitoring and detection solutions in the areas of security, operations and application management. It delivers on providing groundbreaking solutions using smart technologies together with highly skilled people.</p>

<p>In this regard, Exponªnt ISS is the master reseller in Sub-Saharan Africa for Splunk.</p>

<p>In addition, it is a reseller for many global security brands such as AlienVault, a provider of unified security management solutions; Check Point Software Technologies, a provider of IT network security solutions; Imperva, a provider of application and database security solutions; Palo Alto Networks, a provider of next-generation firewall solutions; Trend Micro, a provider of antivirus cloud computing security and internet content security software; and, WebSense, a provider of Internet access management software. Like Splunk, many of these companies are publicly listed and are leaders in their own specific market segments.</p>

<p>Although not exclusively focused on any specific markets, Exponªnt is very strong in the engineering, financial, mining and telecommunications sectors.</p>

<p>In South Africa Exponªnt is rated as a level 3 contributor BBBEE company and has a large customer base comprising of numerous companies from both the private and public sectors.</p>

 </html>
  </row>
</dashboard>