<dashboard version='1.1'>
  <label>About</label>
  <row>
	<html><h1>Welcome to Splunk Windows Security Operations Center by INFIGO IS</h1><br />

	This application allows you to see all security relevant information about your Windows servers. The application was built with security officers in mind - almost any information a Windows security officer would like to see is available and visualized.<br />

	Keep in mind that certain logs are not available on Windows operating systems by default. For example, Windows 2003 servers will not log failed authentication attempts by default so this log category has to be manually turned on before logs become available.<br />

	Special attention was given to Windows authentication logs. Since Windows clients normally issue several ticket requests when a user logs in to the domain, this can cause an incorrect number to be displayed if these login events are just visualised. In order to correctly calculate the number of login events, the Windows Security Center application uses Splunk's transactions to summarize such events - see searches used in Active Directory and NTLM dashboards for more information.<br />

	Enjoy - if you have any questions or comments (or ideas how to improve the application), please <b>e-mail</b> us at <a href="mailto:splunk@infigo.hr">splunk@infigo.hr</a>
	</html>
  </row>

  <row>
	<chart>
	  <search id="base">
		  <query>| metadata type=hosts `windowsindex` | fields - lastTime, recentTime, firstTime, type</query>
		</search>
		<title>Top sending servers in selected index</title>
		<option name="charting.chart">pie</option>
		<option name="refresh.display">progressbar</option>
        <option name="charting.seriesColors">[0xa2cc3e, 0x1e93c6, 0xf2b827, 0xd6563c, 0x6a5c9e, 0x31a35f, 0xed8440, 0x3863a0, 0xcc5068, 0x73427f, 0x11a88b, 0xea9600, 0x0e776d, 0xffb380, 0xaa3977, 0x91af27, 0x4453aa, 0x99712b, 0x553577, 0x97bc71, 0xd35c2d, 0x314d5b, 0x99962b, 0x844539, 0x00b290, 0xe2c188, 0xa34a41, 0x44416d, 0xe29847, 0x8c8910, 0x0b416d, 0x774772, 0x3d9988, 0xbdbd5e, 0x5f7396, 0x844539]</option>
	</chart>
	<chart>
	  <search id="base1">
		  <query>| metadata type=sourcetypes `windowsindex` | fields - lastTime, recentTime, firstTime, type</query>
		</search>
    <title>Top sourcetypes in selected index</title>
    <option name="charting.chart">pie</option>
	<option name="refresh.display">progressbar</option>
    <option name="charting.seriesColors">[0xa2cc3e, 0x1e93c6, 0xf2b827, 0xd6563c, 0x6a5c9e, 0x31a35f, 0xed8440, 0x3863a0, 0xcc5068, 0x73427f, 0x11a88b, 0xea9600, 0x0e776d, 0xffb380, 0xaa3977, 0x91af27, 0x4453aa, 0x99712b, 0x553577, 0x97bc71, 0xd35c2d, 0x314d5b, 0x99962b, 0x844539, 0x00b290, 0xe2c188, 0xa34a41, 0x44416d, 0xe29847, 0x8c8910, 0x0b416d, 0x774772, 0x3d9988, 0xbdbd5e, 0x5f7396, 0x844539]</option>
  	</chart>
  </row>

  <row>
        <html><h1>About INFIGO IS d.o.o.</h1><br />

        <b>INFIGO IS</b> is a leading security company in Croatia. Our services include security assessments (<b>penetration testing, vulnerability assessments</b>), <b>compliance consulting services</b> (ISO 27001/PCIDSS) and <b>security product integration</b> and <b>support</b>, including (of course) Splunk.<br />Read more about INFIGO IS at <a href="https://www.infigo.hr/en/">https://www.infigo.hr/en</a> or contact us at <a href="mailto:infigoapps@infigo.hr">infigoapps@infigo.hr</a>.
        </html>
  </row>
</dashboard>