<dashboard version="1.1">
    <label>Help &amp; About</label>

    <row>
        <panel>
            <html>
                <h2>Suricata SOC Investigation</h2>

                <p>
                    This app turns Suricata IDS alerts in Splunk into an investigation-focused SOC
                    workspace.
                    It helps analysts move from high-level alert monitoring into host, attacker,
                    tactic, and
                    timeline-based investigation.
                </p>

                <h3>What This App Does</h3>

                <ul>
                    <li>Summarises Suricata alert activity across time, source, target, protocol,
                        and severity.</li>
                    <li>Supports analyst investigation by source IP and destination IP.</li>
                    <li>Reconstructs short attack sessions into an incident timeline view.</li>
                    <li>Maps Suricata signatures to MITRE ATT&amp;CK techniques and tactics using a
                        CSV lookup.</li>
                    <li>Highlights unmapped signatures so MITRE coverage can be improved over time.</li>
                    <li>Calculates simple target risk scores based on alert severity and frequency.</li>
                    <li>Provides anomaly-focused dashboards and scheduled detections for unusual
                        behaviour.</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>Recommended Workflow</h3>

                <ul>
                    <li>Set the app-wide <b>Search Scope</b> and <b>Time Range</b> from the
                        <b>Search Scope</b> page if your Suricata data is not in
                        <code>index=suricata</code>.</li>
                    <li>Start with <b>Anomaly Detection</b> or <b>Suricata Overview</b> to identify
                        spikes, noisy sources, important signatures, or heavily targeted hosts.</li>
                    <li>Use <b>Target Risk Scoring</b> to decide which destination hosts need
                        attention first.</li>
                    <li>Use the <b>MITRE ATT&amp;CK</b> dashboards to understand tactics and improve
                        mapping coverage.</li>
                    <li>Use <b>Suricata Investigation</b> and <b>Incident Timeline</b> when you are
                        ready to investigate a source, target, or attack session in detail.</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>Dashboards</h3>

                <ul>
                    <li><b>Anomaly Detection</b> - Find unusual event volume, noisy sources, and
                        frequently seen signatures.</li>
                    <li><b>Suricata Overview</b> - Review alert trends, top signatures, top
                        sources, targeted hosts, protocols, scanner behaviour, and recent alerts.</li>
                    <li><b>Target Risk Scoring</b> - Rank destination hosts by alert severity and
                        activity so analysts can prioritise response.</li>
                    <li><b>MITRE ATT&amp;CK Mapping</b> - View Suricata activity by MITRE tactics,
                        techniques, and mapped signatures.</li>
                    <li><b>Unknown MITRE Coverage</b> - Find alert signatures that are not yet
                        mapped to MITRE ATT&amp;CK.</li>
                    <li><b>MITRE Lookup Editor</b> - Search, add, update, and delete MITRE mappings
                        from inside the app.</li>
                    <li><b>Suricata Investigation</b> - Investigate activity by source IP and
                        destination IP.</li>
                    <li><b>Incident Timeline</b> - Reconstruct short attack sessions for a selected
                        source.</li>
                    <li><b>Search Scope</b> - Save the app-wide default search scope and time range,
                        and preview matching events.</li>
                    <li><b>Help &amp; About</b> - Read this guide, troubleshooting notes, and support
                        information.</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>Before You Start</h3>

                <ul>
                    <li>Make sure Suricata alert data is searchable in Splunk.</li>
                    <li>Use the <b>Search Scope</b> dashboard to confirm the app is looking at the
                        right index, sourcetype, source, or other base filter.</li>
                    <li>If your data is not in <code>index=suricata</code>, save a new default
                        search scope before using the other dashboards.</li>
                    <li>MITRE dashboards use the app lookup, so mapping quality improves as you add
                        missing signatures with the <b>MITRE Lookup Editor</b>.</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>Search Scope and Time Range</h3>

                <ul>
                    <li>Use <b>Search Scope</b> to tell the app where your Suricata data is, for
                        example <code>index=suricata</code>, <code>index=suricata2</code>, or
                        <code>source=eve.json</code>.</li>
                    <li>Use <b>Time Range</b> to control how much data each dashboard searches.</li>
                    <li>Save the values on the <b>Search Scope</b> dashboard when you want all
                        dashboards to use the same defaults next time they open.</li>
                    <li>Changing <b>Search Scope</b> or <b>Time Range</b> on another dashboard is
                        useful for one investigation, but it does not change the saved defaults.</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>MITRE Mapping</h3>

                <ul>
                    <li>The app maps Suricata alert signatures to MITRE ATT&amp;CK tactics and
                        techniques.</li>
                    <li>If a signature is not mapped yet, it appears as <b>Unknown</b> in the MITRE
                        dashboards.</li>
                    <li>The <b>Unknown MITRE Coverage</b> dashboard is designed to help you identify
                        and add missing mappings.</li>
                    <li>Use the <b>MITRE Lookup Editor</b> to improve coverage over time as new
                        signatures appear in your environment.</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>Using the MITRE Lookup Editor</h3>

                <ul>
                    <li>Open <b>MITRE ATT&amp;CK</b> &gt; <b>MITRE Lookup Editor</b> to manage the
                        lookup from inside the app.</li>
                    <li>Use <b>Filter Only</b> mode when you only want to search or review current
                        mappings.</li>
                    <li>Use the <b>Filter Lookup Table</b> field to search across signature,
                        technique ID, technique name, tactic, and description. Use wildcards for
                        partial matches, for example <code>*scan*</code>, <code>T104*</code>, or
                        <code>*Discovery*</code>.</li>
                    <li>Switch to <b>Edit Lookup</b> mode to add a new mapping or update an
                        existing one.</li>
                    <li>Click an existing table row to load that mapping into the edit fields, then
                        change the values and submit.</li>
                    <li>To add a new entry, enter the signature and mapping details, then submit.</li>
                    <li>To delete an entry, load or type the signature, select <b>Delete this
                        signature</b>, then submit.</li>
                    <li>Use <b>Clear fields</b> to reset the editor fields and return the table
                        filter to <code>*</code>.</li>
                    <li>If Splunk shows a warning for <code>outputlookup</code>, that is expected
                        when saving lookup changes. Only users who are allowed to edit lookups
                        should run the save action.</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>Troubleshooting</h3>

                <ul>
                    <li>If dashboards are empty, first check the <b>Search Scope</b> and <b>Time
                        Range</b>.</li>
                    <li>If only MITRE panels show <b>Unknown</b>, open <b>Unknown MITRE Coverage</b>
                        and add missing mappings with the <b>MITRE Lookup Editor</b>.</li>
                    <li>If new dashboard changes do not appear, restart Splunk or refresh the app
                        after redeploying files.</li>
                    <li>If alerts appear incomplete, confirm that your Suricata data is being parsed
                        correctly in Splunk.</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>Support</h3>

                <p>
                    Developer: Kaled Aljebur<br />
                    Email: kaledaljebur@gmail.com<br />
                    Contact me if you need a customised version of this app or a custom Splunk app
                    for your environment.
                </p>

                <h3>Version</h3>

                <p>Suricata SOC Investigation - Version 1.1.1</p>
            </html>
        </panel>
    </row>

</dashboard>
