<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<dashboard>
  <label>ADVISOR Reports</label>
  <row>
    <html>
		<h1><img src="/static/app/EQALIS_Advisor/appIcon.png" alt="Icon" />
			Welcome to EQALIS ADVISOR. This application has reports and alerts to help you manage your Splunk installation.
			<img alt=" " src="http://www.eqalis.com/_apps/EQAD2.0.gif" height="1px" width="1px" />
		</h1>
		<table width="100%" border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" vallign="top">
			<tr valign="top">
				<td width="50%"><br></br><h2>Hosts No Longer Forwarding</h2>
					<p style="margin-right:10px">On larger installations it can become more of a challenge to spot when a Splunk forwarder is no longer forwarding.  The host reports below inform you about hosts that have previously been sending data, but which have not sent any data in the 24 hours.</p>
					<br></br>
					<h2>License Violations</h2>
						<p style="margin-right:10px">Enterprise users who exceed their permitted daily indexing limit will receive a license violation.  After 5 or more license violations (3 if using free license) in a rolling 30-day period search will become disabled.  The license reports inform you about how many violations you currently have and the percentage of license used over the last 7 days.  In addition an email alert can be configured to email you every time the license violation counter increases.</p>
				</td>
				<td width="50%" >
					<p><h2>Notes:</h2></p>
					<p style="margin-right:10px"><strong>1.</strong>  The counters will change colour depending on the value found as follows:
						<ul><pre>
							<li>0   = green</li>
							<li>1-2 = yellow</li>
							<li>3   = orange</li>
							<li>4+  = red</li>
						  </pre>
						</ul>
					</p>
					<p style="margin-right:10px"><strong>2.</strong>  This application's setup screen will have asked for your email address the first time it ran.  Assuming you have configured email settings correctly, you will be sent an email whenever you have a new license violation. <em>You can change the email address(es) by going to &quot;Manager&quot; -&gt; &quot;Apps&quot; -&gt; &quot;Setup&quot; on the line starting &quot;EQALIS Advisor&quot;  and change the  Email address.</em></p>
					<p style="margin-right:10px"><strong>3.</strong>  Some times you will not want hosts showing up in these reports because they are decommissioned or inactive. If this is the case, please tag them as &quot;inactive&quot;. <em>Under each event in a search there is a drop-down menu next to the hostname where you can select “Tag host” and then enter a tag of “inactive”.</em></p>
					<p style="margin-right:10px; text-align:right"> &#169;<a href="http://www.eqalis.com"> EQALIS  2010</a></p>
				</td>
			</tr>
		</table>
    </html>
  </row>
  <row>
    <single>
      <searchName>EQADVISOR - count hosts not forwarding for n time</searchName>
      <title>Hosts not forwarding within the last day</title>
      <option name="classField">range</option>
      <option name="field">count</option>
    </single>
	<single>
      <searchName>EQADVISOR - count of current license violations</searchName>
      <title>Number of current license violations</title>
      <option name="classField">range</option>
      <option name="field">Violations</option>
    </single>
  </row>
  <row>
    <table>
      <searchName>EQADVISOR - table of hosts not forwarding for n time</searchName>
      <title>Hosts not forwarding data for &gt;1 day</title>
      <option name="showPager">true</option>
      <option name="drilldown">none</option>
    </table>
    <chart>
      <searchName>EQADVISOR - Chart Percentage License Used Last Week</searchName>
      <title>% of License Used for Last Week</title>
      <option name="drilldown">all</option>
      <option name="height">298px</option>
    </chart>
  </row>
</dashboard>
