<dashboard version="1.1" theme="light">
  <label>About Dropzone AI</label>

  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
        <h2 style="margin-bottom: 10px;">What is Dropzone AI?</h2>
        <p>
          <strong>Dropzone AI</strong> is a modern security automation platform built to streamline triage, enrichment, and response
          workflows for security operations teams. It helps eliminate manual toil and accelerates decision-making
          by integrating AI-driven context and automation directly into your detection and response pipelines.
        </p>

        <div style="text-align: center; margin-top: 20px; margin-bottom: 20px;">
          <img src="/static/app/dropzone_add_on/images/knowledge.png" style="width: 100%; max-width: 800px; height: auto; border: 1px solid #ddd;" alt="Three Pillars of AI SOC Analysts"/>
        </div>

        <h3 style="margin-top: 20px;">How does this Splunk Add-on help?</h3>
        <ul>
          <li>Performs <strong>health checks</strong> against a Dropzone AI instance to validate connectivity and availability.</li>
          <li>Collects <strong>investigation data</strong> including conclusions, attack surfaces, alert types, and executive summaries.</li>
          <li>Provides <strong>dashboards</strong> to visualize health status, investigation trends, and security insights.</li>
          <li>Enables <strong>search and analysis</strong> of Dropzone AI data alongside your other security events in Splunk.</li>
          <li>Supports integration of Dropzone AI's AI-driven security automation into your Splunk workflows.</li>
        </ul>

        <h3 style="margin-top: 20px;">Getting Started</h3>
        <ol>
          <li>Navigate to the <strong>Inputs</strong> page in the Dropzone AI Add-on.</li>
          <li>Click <strong>Create New Input</strong> and select <strong>Dropzone AI Health Check</strong> to monitor instance health:
            <ul>
              <li>Enter a unique <strong>Name</strong> for the input (e.g., "dropzonehealthchecker")</li>
              <li>Set the <strong>Interval</strong> in seconds (e.g., 60 for 1 minute)</li>
              <li>Select an <strong>Index</strong> where data will be stored (e.g., "main")</li>
              <li>Enter your <strong>Dropzone AI URL</strong> (e.g., https://app.dropzone.ai)</li>
              <li><strong>API Key</strong> is optional for health checks</li>
            </ul>
          </li>
          <li>Click <strong>Create New Input</strong> again and select <strong>Dropzone AI Investigations</strong> to collect investigation data:
            <ul>
              <li>Enter a unique <strong>Name</strong> (e.g., "dropzoneinvestigation")</li>
              <li>Set the <strong>Interval</strong> in seconds (e.g., 300 for 5 minutes)</li>
              <li>Select an <strong>Index</strong> (e.g., "default")</li>
              <li>Enter your <strong>Dropzone AI URL</strong></li>
              <li>Enter your <strong>API Key</strong> in the format: <code>Api-Key YOUR_KEY</code> (required for investigations)</li>
            </ul>
          </li>
          <li>Click <strong>Add</strong> to create each input.</li>
          <li>Activate both inputs using the toggle switches in the <strong>Status</strong> column.</li>
          <li>Verify that health check and investigation events are being indexed (search for <code>sourcetype=dropzone:healthcheck</code> and <code>sourcetype=dropzone:investigation</code>).</li>
          <li>View the <strong>Status</strong> dashboard to monitor availability and the <strong>Investigations</strong> dashboard to analyze investigation data.</li>
        </ol>
        
        <h3 style="margin-top: 20px;">Data Collection</h3>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Health Checks:</strong> Monitors Dropzone AI instance availability (no API key required).</li>
          <li><strong>Investigations:</strong> Pulls completed investigations including conclusions, attack surfaces, alert details, and analysis summaries (API key required).</li>
        </ul>

        <p style="margin-top: 20px;">
          For more information, contact your Dropzone AI representative.
        </p>

        <div style="text-align: center; margin-top: 30px;">
          <img src="/static/app/TA-dropzone-add-on-for-splunk/images/dropzone.png" style="width: 50%; height: auto; border: 1px solid #ddd;" alt="Dropzone AI Screenshot"/>
        </div>
      </html>
    </panel>
  </row>
</dashboard>

