<setup>
	<block title="Configure the R&#38;S&#174;Web Application Firewall for Splunk">
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
		  This Splunk application is designed to work with data source from R&S®Web Application Firewall. You can access to this information page any time in the "Manage Apps" menu.
			
			]]>
		</text>
	</block>
	
	<block title="Configure the macro of your index for search/query">

		<text>
You will need to config index for this application by the following action:
			<![CDATA[
    <ul>
    <li>In Splunk Web, click Settings, then click Advanced search.</li>
    <li>Next, select "Search macros" and "R&S®Web Application Firewall" app from dropdown list</li>
    <li>Select "default_index" and type your index in format: index=<your_index>.</li>
    </ul>
			]]>
		</text>
	</block>

	<block title="Configure the data inputs and source type">

		<text>
        In order to see the logs from R&#38;S&#174;Web Application Firewall, you will have to configure a data input connected with the source type "rswaf" (you can use default index or your index).
			<![CDATA[
      <ul>
			<li> If your splunk server is only intended to process logs from R&S®Web Application Firewall, then just create a data input on the protocol/port you wish (e.g. UDP 514) and select "rswaf" in the list of source types.</li>
      <li> If your splunk server is retreiving logs from other sources, then you can dedicate a listening port to your boxes. Just create a new data input on that port and select "rswaf" in the list of source types.</li>
      <li> If your splunk server is retreiving logs from other sources and you need to use the same listening port for boxes. Then you will have to delete that global data input, create one data input by box, restricted to its IP address and mapped to the "rswaf" source type. Finally, recreate the global data input initialy deleted.</li>
      </ul>   
			]]>
        In the future, remember that if you want to create a customised dashboards, you will need to specify "`default_index` sourcetype=rswaf" in your queries. 
          
		</text>
	</block>
	
	<block title="Configure syslog alerts on R&#38;S&#174;Web Application Firewall">
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
       Connect to the management box with the gui interface and navigate to Management > Alerting.<br>
       First of all, you will need to declare the splunk server as a new alerting profile. Clic on "Alerting Profile" and "Add". Specify the profile name (e.g. "splunk"), the IP address of the splunk server, the port and protocol you configured in the data input section just above (e.g. UDP 514).<br>
       Now you can do the following actions :<br>
      <ul>
			<li> To store event logs, clic on "Event Log Destination" and "Add". enter a name and select the splunk destination. Clic on the Filters tab and adjust the logs.</li>
      <li> To configure delayed log alerting, clic on "Log Alerting configurations", specify the frequency in minutes, leave format as default and select the splunk server as destination.</li>
      <li> To configure realtime and access logs, navigate to Setup > Tunnels. Double clic on the tunnel and select the "Logs" tab. Select the types of logs you need and the splunk server as destination. If asked, the alerting format must be set to <b>Default</b></li>
      </ul>   
        Finally, apply your configuration changes. No reboot is needed.<br>
        If you need help about configuring syslog alerts, you will find usefull information in the product knowledge base. 
			]]>
        
 		</text>
	</block>
	
	
	<block title="Geolocation Lookup" endpoint="admin/localapps/" entity="MAXMIN[D]" mode="iter">
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
			You will need to install the <a target="_blank" onclick="return openAppPage('Geo+Location+Lookup+Script');" href="http://apps.splunk.com/app/291/">Geolocation Lookup</a> app in order to translate external IPs to Geo info for the flash maps and geo based reports to work.

<style>#item-blockFieldset-10{ display:none; }</style>
<script type="text/javascript">
 $(document).ready(function() {
   $('#item-blockFieldset-10').hide();
 });
</script>	
			]]> 
		</text>
		<input field="enabled">
			<label>Enable Geolocation Lookup</label>
			<type>bool</type>
		</input>
	</block>

	<block title="HTTP User-Agent parser" endpoint="admin/localapps/" entity="uaparse[r]" mode="iter">
		<text>
			<![CDATA[
			You will need to install the <a target="_blank" onclick="return openAppPage('uaparser');" href="https://splunkbase.splunk.com/app/3003/">HTTP User-Agent parser</a> app in order to extract formated fields from user agents.

<style>#item-blockFieldset-10{ display:none; }</style>
<script type="text/javascript">
 $(document).ready(function() {
   $('#item-blockFieldset-10').hide();
 });
</script>	
			]]> 
		</text>
		<input field="enabled">
			<label>Enable HTTP User-Agent parser</label>
			<type>bool</type>
		</input>
	</block>
		
	<block title="Activate R&#38;S&#174;Web Application Firewall for Splunk" endpoint="admin/localapps/" entity="rswa[f]" mode="iter">
		<input field="enabled">
			<label>Activate R&#38;S&#174;Web Application Firewall for Splunk</label>
			<type>bool</type>
		</input>
	</block>

</setup>
