<setup>
    <block title="Request Destination Fields" endpoint="configs/conf-investigate_integration" entity="data-fields">
        <text>The add-on expects fields that are designated as the destination (i.e. 'dest' or similar). These should be entered in comma separated format.</text>
        <input field="fields">
            <label>Fields</label>
            <type>text</type>
        </input>
    </block>
    <block title="Scheduled Search Name" endpoint="configs/conf-investigate_integration" entity="scheduled-report">
        <input field="report-name">
            <label>Report Name</label>
            <type>text</type>
        </input>
    </block>
    <block title="Set how far back in time you want to save data" endpoint="configs/conf-investigate_integration" entity="timestamp-pruning">
        <text>You may wish to prune older data to limit the size of the data store. In which case, here you define how long you would like save data. The format should be saved as a Splunk time modifier for search. For example, if you wish to save data for a week, you would enter -7d@d. Leaving this blank will disable timestamp pruning.</text>
        <input field="time-modifier">
            <label>Time modifier</label>
            <type>text</type>
        </input>
    </block>
    <block title="Umbrella Top 1 Million Limit" endpoint="configs/conf-investigate_integration" entity="umbrella-exclusion-list">
        <text>If you would like to exclude popular domains from being enriched, you can enter a number here from 1 to 1 million. Doing so will exclude the corresponding top domains in the Umbrella Top 1 Million. For example, if you enter 200, the Add On will not enrich the top 200 domains in the list. Otherwise, leave it blank.</text>
        <input field="umbrella-top-limit">
            <label>Umbrella Top 1 Million Limit</label>
            <type>number</type>
        </input>
    </block>
    <block title="Custom Exclusion List" endpoint="configs/conf-investigate_integration" entity="user-exclusion-list">
        <text>If you would like to specifically exclude certain IOCs from ever being enriched, enter them in comma-separated format below. They can be domains, IPs, or file hashes. If a domain, all subdomains will also be excluded from enrichment. Otherwise, leave it blank.</text>
        <input field="excluded-entities">
            <label>Exclude</label>
            <type>text</type>
        </input>
    </block>
    <block title="Set how much data you want to save" endpoint="configs/conf-investigate_integration" entity="size-pruning">
        <text>You may wish to prune data not to exceed a specific number of rows. Set the max number of rows here. Anything excess will be deleted in time-ascending order (i.e. oldest first). Leaving this blank will disable size pruning.</text>
        <input field="size-pruning-max">
            <label>Max number of rows</label>
            <type>number</type>
        </input>
    </block>
    <block title="Proxies" endpoint="configs/conf-investigate_integration" entity="proxy">
        <text>Set the IP and port of your proxy server. If this is blank, the add-on will make direct requests to the investigate api. Make sure to use the following format: ip:port. Only IP and port are required, not protocol.</text>
        <input field="proxy-address">
            <label>EX: 0.0.0.0:3128</label>
            <type>text</type>
        </input>
    </block>
    <block title="Host name" endpoint="configs/conf-investigate_integration" entity="network">
        <text>Set the Splunk management server's host name, if different from this host</text>
        <input field="host">
            <label>Host name</label>
            <type>text</type>
        </input>
    </block>
    <block title="Port" endpoint="configs/conf-investigate_integration" entity="network">
        <text>Set the Splunk management port</text>
        <input field="port">
            <label>Port</label>
            <type>number</type>
        </input>
    </block>
</setup>
