
<dashboard version="2" theme="dark">
    <label>Splunk App for Kubernetes — User Guide</label>
    <description></description>
    <definition><![CDATA[
{
	"visualizations": {
		"viz_TcgzXHEI": {
			"type": "splunk.markdown",
			"options": {
				"markdown": "## What is this app?\n\nThis SEARCH HEAD only app gives you live visibility into your Kubernetes clusters directly inside Splunk. It shows node health, pod status, resource usage, and workload behaviour — all fed automatically by the **Splunk OpenTelemetry Collector** running inside your cluster. Most panels should start working out of the box when you use the Splunk OpenTelemetry Collector. Check out the github page for sample values.yaml for configuration examples of the Splunk OTEL Collector helm chart.\n\nYOU SHOULD KNOW WHICH INDEXES IS YOUR TELEMETRY IS GETTING INTO. \nYOU SHOULD UPDATE THOSE INDEXES IN THE LOOKUP FILES. READ BELOW.\n\n\n---\n\n## Where does the telemetry come from? How to add more indexes that receive OTEL Telemetry in this app's contexts?\n\nThe app reads from the indexes that are defined in the index Lookup files. Various indexes that receive telemetry from the OTEL Collector can be updated in the lookup file one time and you should see the indexes populate across the dashboards.\n\n- k8s_logs_events_indexes_dropdown_lookup.csv\n- k8s_metrics_indexes_dropdown_lookup.csv\n\nBoth the look up files are packaged as part of this app. You can use apps like Splunk App for Lookup File Editing to add indexes to the list. Multiple indexes can be included as part of a single row, just make sure the value for such multi-index keys are appropriately set as given in the default examples.\n\nThe metrics lookup file should be populated with metrics indexes and the logs_events look up file should be populated for populating all logs, Kubernetes events and traces data so that the panels are populated automatically across the dashboards.\n\n> Refer to the other tab on the dashboard for a reference to required changes in values.yaml in Splunk OTEL Collector helm chart. These changes are required for the panels to show the data, especially the ones related to labels and metadata collection changes\n\n---\n\n## Best Practices\n\n### Keep time ranges short and focused\nThe dashboards use `| mstats` queries that scan metric indexes — wider time ranges mean significantly more data scanned and slower load times. Stick to **last 60 minutes** for real-time monitoring and **last 4–6 hours** for trend analysis. Only go wider (e.g. last 24 hours) when you genuinely need historical context, and narrow back down when done.\n\n### Always filter by cluster and namespace\nLeaving **Cluster** and **Namespace** set to `*` runs every query across all clusters and all namespaces simultaneously. On a busy Splunk instance this puts unnecessary load on the search head. Pick the specific cluster and namespace you care about before reading the panels.\n\n### Avoid searching across multiple indexes unnecessarily\nThe Metrics Index dropdown includes options like `k8s_metrics OR index=custom_metrics`. Only select these combined options if you know data lives in both indexes. Searching two indexes doubles the scan cost with no benefit if the second index is empty or irrelevant.\n\n### Don't run detail dashboards with `*` on the workload selector\nDashboards like Deployments, DaemonSets, and StatefulSets have a workload-specific dropdown (e.g. select a deployment name). Leaving it as `*` loads resource data for every workload in the namespace at once — useful occasionally for a broad check, but expensive. Select the specific workload you want to monitor day-to-day.\n\n### Use the dashboard refresh, not manual re-runs\nAll panels auto-refresh every 61–65 seconds. There is no need to navigate away and back to refresh data. Repeatedly opening and closing dashboards creates redundant concurrent searches.\n\n### Set a throttle on every alert\nWhen creating alerts from panel queries, always configure a **throttle / suppression window** (15–30 minutes minimum). Kubernetes conditions like pod restarts or high CPU are often transient — without throttling, a single flapping pod can generate dozens of alert emails within minutes.\n\n### Don't schedule too many alerts at the same interval\nIf you create multiple alerts all scheduled at the same time (e.g. all at `*/5 * * * *`), they all execute simultaneously on the Splunk search head. Stagger alert schedules by a minute or two — for example, one at `:00`, the next at `:01`, and so on.\n\n### Narrow the time range in alerts\nWhen an alert is based on a dashboard panel query, the default `earliest` and `latest` from the dashboard may be wide (e.g. last 4 hours). For most operational alerts you only need to look back **5–10 minutes** (matching your schedule frequency). Use `earliest=-5m latest=now` to keep alert searches fast.\n\n### Avoid running the HPA dashboard with a very short time range\nThe HPA dashboard's scaling history and latency panels rely on Kubernetes event logs. Scaling events are infrequent — if you set the time range to last 5 minutes you will likely see empty panels. Use **last 4 hours** or wider as the default for this dashboard.\n\n### Don't use the app as your primary log search tool\n\nThe event log panels (Recent Events, Recent DaemonSet Events, etc.) show a limited tail of events (`| head 15` to `| head 100`). They are for quick context only. For full log investigation, go to **Search & Reporting** directly and query `index=k8s_logs` with proper filters.\n\n---\n\n## Inputs — What to select before reading a dashboard\n\nEvery dashboard has a toolbar at the top with filter inputs. Always set these first:\n\n- **Time Range** — Controls the window of data shown. Default is last 60 minutes.\n- **Metrics Index** — Which index to query. Use `k8s_metrics` unless you have a custom index.\n- **Cluster** — Filters to a specific EKS/K8s cluster. Select your cluster from the dropdown.\n- **Namespace** — Narrows to one namespace. Leave as `*` for all, or pick a specific one.\n- **Workload** — (Detail dashboards only) Filters to a specific deployment, daemonset, statefulset, or HPA.\n- **Event Logs Index** — Which index event logs come from. Use `k8s_logs` or `*` for all.\n\n> **Tip:** The Cluster and Namespace dropdowns are populated dynamically — they only show clusters/namespaces that have sent data in the current time window. If a cluster doesn't appear, widen the time range.\n\n---\n\n## Dashboard by Dashboard\n\n### Cluster Overview\n**What you see:** The \"big picture\" health of your entire cluster in one view.\n- **KPI tiles** at the top: Total nodes, % healthy nodes, total pods, % running pods, cluster CPU and memory utilisation\n- **Resource timeline** — CPU cores and memory % over time (last 24 h by default)\n- **Top namespaces** by CPU and memory — horizontal bar charts showing which teams/apps consume the most\n- **Node status table** — each node with Ready/NotReady status, CPU usage, and pod count\n- **Recent Kubernetes events** — last 15 cluster-wide events (warnings, errors, scheduling issues)\n- **Top 10 pods by CPU and memory** — quickly spot runaway containers\n\n---\n\n### Nodes\n**What you see:** Deep-dive into one or all nodes in the cluster.\n- **KPI tiles**: Total nodes, Ready nodes, Not Ready nodes, avg CPU cores in use, avg memory in use (MB)\n- **CPU / Memory timelines** — per-node trend lines side by side\n- **Node capacity table** — allocatable CPU cores and memory GB per node\n- **Disk usage over time** — filesystem % per node\n- **Pod distribution** — how many pods are scheduled on each node (column chart)\n- **Node network I/O** — TX/RX MB/s per node\n- **Node conditions** — Ready/NotReady/Unknown status for the selected node\n- **Recent node events** — last 20 events for the selected node\n\n> Select a specific node in the **Select Node** dropdown to see its conditions and events. Leave as `*` to compare across all nodes.\n\n---\n\n### Workloads — Overview\n**What you see:** A cross-workload snapshot across your namespace — deployments, statefulsets, daemonsets, jobs all in one place.\n- **KPI tiles**: Avg pod CPU (cores), avg pod memory (MB), failed pods count, pending pods count\n- **Pod CPU utilisation over time** — top 10 pods by CPU % as line chart\n- **Deployment replica status** — table of every deployment with desired vs available replicas, coloured Healthy/Degraded/Unhealthy\n- **Container status by pod** — each container's Ready/Not Ready state\n- **Pod details table** — full list of pods with Status, CPU, memory, restart count (rows colour-coded by status)\n\n> Use the **Workload Type** dropdown to filter to just Deployments, StatefulSets, DaemonSets, or Jobs.\n\n---\n\n### Deployments\n**What you see:** Health and resource usage for a single deployment.\n- **KPI tiles**: Health score %, desired replicas, available replicas, avg CPU, avg memory\n- **Replica status over time** — desired vs ready vs available as a line chart\n- **CPU per pod** / **Memory per pod** — individual pod trend lines\n- **CPU requests vs actual usage** — stacked column chart per pod (blue = request, orange = actual)\n- **Memory requests vs actual usage** — same pattern for memory\n- **Pod details table** — pod-by-pod status, CPU, memory, restarts\n- **Resource allocation summary** — CPU request/limit/usage and memory request/limit/usage per pod\n- **Recent deployment events** — last 20 Kubernetes events for this deployment's pods\n- **Container status by pod** — per-container ready state\n\n---\n\n### DaemonSets\n**What you see:** Health of a daemonset across all nodes it runs on.\n- **KPI tiles**: Health score %, desired on nodes, current on nodes, misscheduled, total restarts, avg CPU, avg memory\n- **Replica status over time** — desired vs current vs misscheduled over time\n- **CPU per pod** / **Memory per pod** — per-node-pod trend lines\n- **CPU requests vs usage** / **Memory requests vs usage** — allocation efficiency\n- **Per-node pod status** — table showing which node has which pod and whether it is Running/Pending\n- **Pod details table** — status, CPU, memory, restarts per pod\n- **Pod restart counts** — column chart to spot crashlooping pods\n- **Resource allocation summary** — per-pod request/limit/usage\n- **Pod age analysis** — how long each pod has been running (days/hours)\n- **Network I/O** — aggregate MB/s for all daemonset pods\n- **Container status by pod** — container-level ready state\n- **Recent daemonset events** — last 20 events\n\n---\n\n### StatefulSets\n**What you see:** Same depth as Deployments but tailored for ordered, identity-aware pods.\n- All the same panels as Deployments (health score, replicas, CPU/memory, requests vs usage, events)\n- **Pod age** — StatefulSets are long-lived; this shows how long each ordinal pod has been up\n- **Network I/O** — aggregate traffic across all StatefulSet pods\n\n---\n\n### Jobs / CronJobs\n**What you see:** Completion tracking and resource usage for batch workloads.\n- **KPI tiles**: Job completion rate %, target completions, successful completions, active pods, failed pods, total pod restarts, avg CPU, avg memory\n- **Replica status over time** — desired vs successful vs active vs failed as coloured line chart\n- **CPU per pod** (column) / **Memory per pod** (line) — resource usage during job execution\n- **CPU requests vs usage** / **Memory requests vs usage** — allocation efficiency\n- **Pod restart counts** — identify crashlooping job pods\n- **Pod status table** — per-pod status with colour-coded rows and restart heat-map\n- **Container status by pod** — container-level ready state\n- **Recent job events** — last 20 Kubernetes events\n\n---\n\n### HPAs (Horizontal Pod Autoscaler)\n**What you see:** Whether autoscaling is working correctly for a workload.\n- **KPI tiles**: HPA health status %, current replicas, desired replicas, min replicas, max replicas, scaling events in last 1h\n- **Replica count over time** — current, desired, min, and max as a line chart — the key chart to see scale-up/down activity\n- **Workload CPU usage** — CPU trend for pods managed by this HPA\n- **Pod count distribution** — column chart of pod count over time (hourly)\n- **HPA metrics summary** — table of all raw HPA metrics (current CPU %, target CPU %, etc.)\n- **Scaling decision latency** — time between a threshold breach and the actual scaling action\n- **Scaling activity** — scale-up vs scale-down events per hour (stacked column)\n- **Recent scaling decisions** — table of the last 20 ScaledUp/ScaledDown events with timestamps\n\n> Set the time range to **Last 4 hours** or wider to see scaling patterns. The default is `-4h`.\n\n---\n### 💰 Cost Efficiency Dashboard\n\n- Gives a quick view of Kubernetes resource waste and potential savings using top-level efficiency KPIs.\n- Identifies over-provisioned and under-provisioned pods to guide right-sizing actions.\n- Shows which namespaces and workload types are driving the most wasted CPU/memory.\n- Highlights practical waste signals such as idle pods, missing limits, underutilized PVs, and high restart counts.\n- Helps teams run periodic optimization reviews with filters for time range, cluster, namespace, and metrics index.\n\n---\n### Trace Visibility Dashboard\n- Provides high-level tracing health with total traces/spans, error rate, and latency KPIs (including P95/P99).\n- Tracks performance trends over time using trace volume, latency percentile, and error-rate timelines.\n- Compares service behavior with per-service latency and request-rate views to find slow or overloaded services.\n- Surfaces troubleshooting clues through span duration distribution, HTTP status distribution, and slow operations.\n- Supports release validation and incident debugging with filters for time range, trace index, cluster, and service scope.\n---\n\n## How to Create Alerts from Dashboard Panels\n\nAny panel's SPL query can be turned into a Splunk alert. Here's how:\n\n### Step 1 — Find the query you want to alert on\n\nIn Splunk Dashboard Studio, click on a panel → **Edit** → **Data Sources** tab → copy the SPL query. Alternatively you can find it in the XML files under views.\n\n### Step 2 — Open the app context where you want the alert created and run the query\n\nPaste the query into the search bar and adjust for the condition you want to alert on. For example, to alert when failed pods > 0:\n\n```spl\n| mstats latest(_value) as phase\n  WHERE index=k8s_metrics metric_name=k8s.pod.phase\n  k8s.cluster.name=splunk-development-eks\n  by k8s.pod.name\n| stats count(eval(phase==4 OR phase==\"Failed\")) as failed_pods\n| where failed_pods > 0\n```\n\n### Step 3 — Save as Alert\n\nClick **Save As → Alert** and configure:\n\nWhen configuring the alert, use these settings:\n\n- **Alert type** — Scheduled (e.g. every 5 minutes)\n- **Trigger condition** — Number of results > 0\n- **Trigger actions** — Email / Slack webhook / PagerDuty\n- **Throttle** — Suppress after triggering for 15–30 minutes to avoid noise\n\n---\n\n### Alternate method — Open directly from a dashboard panel\n\nInstead of copying the SPL manually, you can launch the search straight from the panel:\n\n1. Open the dashboard and set your inputs (cluster, namespace, time range)\n2. Hover over the panel you want to alert on — a **magnifying glass** appears in the bottom-right corner of the panel\n3. Click it and this opens Search with the panel's query pre-loaded and the current token values already substituted\n4. Adjust the query if needed (e.g. add a `| where` condition to define your alert threshold)\n5. Click **Save As → Alert** and configure as above\n6. If your team owns a different app which manage all the alerts, take the query and create an alert in that app\n\nThis is the quickest path since you skip the copy-paste step and the tokens are already resolved to real values.\n\n### Useful alerts to create from this app\n\n**Pods stuck in Failed state** — Based on the Workloads pod details table. Trigger when `phase==4` count > 0.\n\n**Node NotReady** — Based on the Cluster Overview node status panel. Trigger when `ready_val==0` count > 0.\n\n**High pod restart count** — Based on the pod restart counts panel in any workload dashboard. Trigger when `restart_count > 5`.\n\n**HPA at max replicas** — Based on the HPAs replica count panel. Trigger when `current_replicas == max_replicas`.\n\n**DaemonSet misscheduled** — Based on the DaemonSets replica status panel. Trigger when `misscheduled > 0`.\n\n**Job failure rate** — Based on the Jobs completion rate panel. Trigger when `health_score < 70`.\n\n**Node CPU high** — Based on the Nodes CPU timeline panel. Trigger when `avg_cpu` exceeds your defined threshold.\n\n### Step 4 — Pass tokens as literal values\n\nDashboard queries use tokens like `$cluster_token$`. When saving as an alert, replace tokens with real values:\n\n```spl\n-- In dashboard:\nmetric_name=k8s.pod.phase k8s.cluster.name=$cluster_token$ k8s.namespace.name=$namespace_token$\n\n-- In alert:\nmetric_name=k8s.pod.phase k8s.cluster.name=splunk-development-eks k8s.namespace.name=production\n```"
			}
		},
		"viz_jWl9axYu": {
			"type": "splunk.markdown",
			"options": {
				"markdown": "## Splunk OTel Collector `values.yaml` Change Summary\n\nSplunk OTEL Collector Original Helm Chartis available at [https://github.com/signalfx/splunk-otel-collector-chart](https://github.com/signalfx/splunk-otel-collector-chart)\n\nThis document lists mandatory `values.yaml`  changes from a basic/default chart configuration into a more complete **AWS EKS-focused Splunk OpenTelemetry deployment configuration**.\n\n> Depending on the flavour of Kubernetes and hosting service, you can apply the settings accordingly. For ex, you may have to use cloud provider as azure if you are using Azure AKS. Refer to the [original documentation mentioned in the packaged values.yaml](https://github.com/signalfx/splunk-otel-collector-chart/blob/main/helm-charts/splunk-otel-collector/values.yaml) for more details.\n\n---\n\n## 1. Splunk Platform output was configured\n\n### Changes made\n- Added a concrete `splunkPlatform.endpoint`\n- Added a HEC `token`\n- Enabled:\n  - `logsEnabled: true`\n  - `metricsEnabled: true`\n  - `tracesEnabled: true`\n- Added dedicated indexes:\n  - `index: k8s_logs`\n  - `metricsIndex: k8s_metrics`\n  - `tracesIndex: k8s_traces`\n- Set `source: kubernetes`\n- Tuned delivery settings such as retries, queueing, timeout, and connection limits\n\n### Purpose\nThis allows the collector to send **logs, metrics, and traces** directly to Splunk Enterprise using HEC, while keeping each telemetry type separated into the correct index. Refer to the chart's documentation for advanced use cases like sending telemetry from various namespaces of a cluster to different indexes etc\n\n---\n\n## 2. AWS and EKS-specific settings were added\n\n### Changes made\n- Set `cloudProvider: aws`\n- Set `distribution: eks`\n- Set `environment: dev`\n\n### Purpose\nThese settings make the chart behave correctly for **Amazon EKS**, enable cloud-aware behavior, and tag telemetry with an environment value for filtering and correlation.\n\n---\n\n## 3. Extra Kubernetes metadata enrichment was added\n\n### Changes made\n- Added `extraAttributes.fromLabels`\n- Included the Kubernetes `app` label as an extra attribute\n\n### Purpose\nThis enriches telemetry with workload metadata so dashboards and searches in Splunk can group and filter data more effectively.\n\n``` yaml\nextraAttributes:\n\n  # Labels that will be collected from k8s pods (or namespaces) (in case they are set)\n  # and added as extra attributes to the telemetry in the following format:\n  # k8s.<pod|namespace>.labels.<label_name>: <label_value>\n  #  For example, if you want to collect \"my_key\" label from your namespaces, you could use the following:\n  #  fromLabels:\n  #    - key: my_key\n  #      from: namespace\n  #\n  #  If you want to change the default attribute name `k8s.pod.labels.<label_name>`, you could do that using a `tag_name` field:\n  #  fromLabels:\n  #    - key: my_key\n  #      tag_name: my_tag\n  #      from: pod\n  #\n  #  `key_regex` field can be used to get a specific set of labels that match a regex.\n  #  If `key_regex` used is used, the `key` field accepts regexp matching groups.\n  #  The following example will fetch all the pod labels and propagate them to the attributes as is,\n  #  without \"k8s.pod.labels.\" prefix. \"$\" from the matching group must be escaped as \"$$\".\n  #  fromLabels:\n  #    - key_regex: (.*)\n  #      from: pod\n  #      tag_name: \"$$1\"\n  fromLabels:\n    - key: app\n```\n---\n\n## 4. The node-level OTel agent was enabled and customized\n\n### Changes made\n- Enabled `agent`\n- Enabled control plane metric collection for:\n  - API server\n  - controller manager\n  - CoreDNS\n  - kube-proxy\n  - scheduler\n- Exposed host ports for, enable if you need them:\n  - OTLP gRPC\n  - OTLP HTTP\n  - Zipkin\n  - Jaeger Thrift\n  - Jaeger gRPC\n- Enabled `hostNetwork: true`\n- Enabled an agent `service`\n- Added `kubeletstats` metric enrichment for:\n  - volumes\n  - nodes\n  - pods\n  - containers\n\n### Purpose\nThis deploys one collector agent per node and allows it to:\n- collect node and control-plane telemetry\n- receive telemetry directly from workloads\n- run within smaller node capacity limits\n- enrich infrastructure metrics with more useful Kubernetes metadata\n``` yaml\nagent:\n  config:\n    receivers:\n      kubeletstats:\n        extra_metadata_labels:\n          - k8s.volume.type\n          - container.id\n        metric_groups:\n          - volume\n          - node\n          - pod\n          - container\n```\n---\n\n## 5. The cluster receiver was enabled and tuned\n\n### Changes made\n- Enabled `clusterReceiver`\n- Enabled `eventsEnabled: true`\n- Added `k8sObjects` collection for pods with a long pull interval\n- Overrode `k8sattributes/metrics.filter.node_from_env_var` to an empty value\n- Added extraction of workload ownership metadata:\n  - deployment name\n  - replicaset name\n  - daemonset name\n  - statefulset name\n  - job name\n  - cronjob name\n  - pod start time\n- Enabled extra cluster metric attributes for:\n  - HPA scale target kind\n  - HPA scale target name\n  - allocatable resource reporting\n  - node condition reporting\n\n### Purpose\nThis creates a dedicated collector for **cluster-wide Kubernetes API telemetry** and ensures pod metrics are enriched with their owning workload information, which improves visibility for Deployments, StatefulSets, DaemonSets, Jobs, CronJobs, and HPAs.\n\n``` yaml\nclusterReceiver:\n  k8sObjects:\n    - name: pods\n      mode: pull\n      interval: 6h\n  config:\n    processors:\n      # Override k8sattributes/metrics to enrich pod metrics with workload owner dimensions.\n      # Default chart config has extract.metadata: [] (empty) and filter restricted to local node.\n      # We remove the node filter so ALL pods in the cluster are enriched, and add owner-reference\n      # metadata so k8s.pod.phase and other pod metrics carry the owning workload's name.\n      k8sattributes/metrics:\n        filter:\n          # Override default \"K8S_NODE_NAME\" to empty - disables node filter so the processor\n          # watches all pods cluster-wide, not just pods on the cluster receiver's node.\n          node_from_env_var: \"\"\n        extract:\n          metadata:\n            - k8s.deployment.name\n            - k8s.replicaset.name\n            - k8s.daemonset.name\n            - k8s.statefulset.name\n            - k8s.job.name\n            - k8s.cronjob.name\n            - k8s.pod.start_time\n    receivers:\n      k8s_cluster:\n        node_conditions_to_report: [Ready, MemoryPressure, DiskPressure, PIDPressure, NetworkUnavailable]\n        allocatable_types_to_report: [cpu, memory, storage, ephemeral-storage]\n        resource_attributes:\n          k8s.hpa.scaletargetref.kind:\n            enabled: true\n          k8s.hpa.scaletargetref.name:\n            enabled: true\n\n```\n\n---\n\n## 6. Native container log collection was enabled\n\n### Changes made\n- Enabled `logsCollection.containers`\n- Set `excludeAgentLogs: true`\n- Kept checkpoint-based log position tracking enabled\n\n### Purpose\nThis allows the collector to ingest Kubernetes container logs while avoiding ingestion loops from the collector’s own logs.\n\n---\n\n## 7. IRSA was configured for AWS access -- only for AWS EKS - apply as needed\n\n### Changes made\n- Added an IAM role annotation under `serviceAccount.annotations`\n\n### Purpose\nThis enables **IAM Roles for Service Accounts (IRSA)** so the collector can access AWS APIs securely without static credentials.\n\n---\n\n## 8. Tolerations were added for wider scheduling coverage (AWS Specific)\n\n### Changes made\n- Added tolerations for:\n  - `node-role.kubernetes.io/master`\n  - `node-role.kubernetes.io/control-plane`\n  - `kubernetes.io/system-node`\n  - `node-role.kubernetes.io/infra`\n\n### Purpose\nThis allows the agent DaemonSet to run on more node types so telemetry coverage is broader across the cluster.\n\n---\n\n## Overall outcome\n\nThese changes turn the chart into a more complete **Splunk OTel deployment in general and specific for AWS EKS** that:\n\n- sends logs, metrics, and traces to Splunk Enterprise\n- runs one agent per node\n- runs a dedicated cluster receiver\n- enriches telemetry with workload metadata\n- uses AWS IRSA for secure cloud access\n\n---\n\n## Important notes\n\n- The file currently contains a **plaintext HEC token** and should ideally use a Kubernetes secret or an external secret source instead.\n- Any non AWS Specfic settings like cluster receiver settings etc should be applied irrespective of the cloud provider or hosting environment so that the dashboards will get populated correctly."
			}
		}
	},
	"defaults": {
		"dataSources": {
			"ds.search": {
				"options": {
					"queryParameters": {
						"latest": "$global_time.latest$",
						"earliest": "$global_time.earliest$"
					}
				}
			}
		},
		"visualizations": {
			"global": {
				"showProgressBar": true
			}
		}
	},
	"layout": {
		"options": {},
		"globalInputs": [],
		"tabs": {
			"items": [
				{
					"layoutId": "layout_1",
					"label": "Main Guide"
				},
				{
					"layoutId": "layout_ytxfrFA1",
					"label": "Splunk OTEL Collector Chart - Changes in values.yaml"
				}
			]
		},
		"layoutDefinitions": {
			"layout_1": {
				"type": "absolute",
				"structure": [
					{
						"item": "viz_TcgzXHEI",
						"type": "block",
						"position": {
							"x": 10,
							"y": 10,
							"w": 1420,
							"h": 4290
						}
					}
				],
				"options": {
					"width": 1440,
					"height": 4300,
					"display": "auto"
				}
			},
			"layout_ytxfrFA1": {
				"type": "absolute",
				"structure": [
					{
						"item": "viz_jWl9axYu",
						"type": "block",
						"position": {
							"x": 10,
							"y": 10,
							"w": 1180,
							"h": 4750
						}
					}
				],
				"options": {
					"height": 4800
				}
			}
		}
	},
	"description": "",
	"title": "Splunk App for Kubernetes — User Guide",
	"applicationProperties": {
		"hideEdit": true,
		"hideOpenInSearch": true,
		"hideExport": true,
		"hideViewModeActionMenu": true
	}
}
    ]]></definition>
</dashboard>
