<setup>
	<block title="The Media Trust License Key"
		endpoint="themediatrust/endpoint"
		entity="setupentity">
	   <text>
		&lt;i&gt;To obtain a paid or trial license key, please email data@themediatrust.com. &lt;/i&gt;
	   </text>

	   <input field="license_key">
		<label>If you already have a license key, enter it below:</label>
		<type>text</type>
	   </input>

	</block>

	<block title="Data Refresh Interval"
		endpoint="themediatrust/endpoint"
		entity="setupentity">
	   <text>
		&lt;i&gt;Refresh data regularly to obtain the most recent, active threat indicators. You can choose a refresh interval between 24 hours (1440 minutes) to 1 hour (60 minutes).  The recommended value is 60 minutes.&lt;/i&gt;
	   </text>
	   <input field="download_interval">
		<label>Specify the number of minutes between data refreshes:</label>
		<type>text</type>
	   </input>
	</block>
	<block title="Indicators Detected in the Last x Days"
		endpoint="themediatrust/endpoint"
		entity="setupentity">
	   <text>
		&lt;i&gt;Enter a value between 2 and 7 days. (Entering a larger number of days may include indicators that are no longer active. For example, entering 3 will include all indicators detected in the past three days. This includes indicators seen three days ago that may not have been seen in the two days since then.) The recommended value is 2 days.&lt;/i&gt;
	   </text>
	   <input field="startdate">
		<label>Specify the number of days for which you would like the detected indicators:</label>
		<type>text</type>
	   </input>
	</block>
	<block title="Report Data to The Media Trust"
		endpoint="themediatrust/endpoint"
		entity="setupentity">
	   <text>
		&lt;i&gt;By reporting aggregated data to The Media Trust, you help us understand how the data is working in your environment. No personal data is collected.&lt;/i&gt;
	   </text>
	   <input field="opt_in">
		<label>I agree to report aggregated data</label>
		<type>bool</type>
	   </input>
	</block>
	<block title="Threat Feed Risk Score"
		endpoint="themediatrust/endpoint"
		entity="setupentity">
	   <text>
		&lt;i&gt;The Media Trust’s malware attack data is collected from our 24/7/365 monitoring of the most heavily-trafficked digital properties, including frequently whitelisted premium websites. The threat data is verified and accurate, enabling you to immediately block threats without further analysis or disruption to user productivity. We recommended that indicators categorized as Blacklist and Watchlist be immediately added to your firewall block list. You may also choose to modify this value to align with your risk scoring strategy. The recommended score for The Media Trust indicators is 100.&lt;/i&gt;
	   </text>
	   <input field="riskscore">
		<label>Specify a Risk Score for assets/identities that interact with feed members:</label>
		<type>text</type>
	   </input>
	</block>
	<block title="Add Credentials to Maintain the Feed"
		endpoint="themediatrust/endpoint"
		entity="setupentity">
	   <text>
		&lt;i&gt;We do some ongoing maintenance of the feed that goes into Splunk and for that we need credentials that are allowed to access lookup files.  As such, please provide us with user credentials that can access the ip_intel lookup.&lt;/i&gt;
	   </text>
	    <input field="uid">
	      <label>Username</label>
	      <type>text</type>
	    </input>
	    <input field="pwd">
	      <label>Password</label>
	      <type>password</type>
	    </input>
	  </block>	
</setup>
