<form>
 <label>Summary</label>

 <fieldset autoRun="true">
  <input type="time" searchWhenChanged="true">
   <default>Last 60 minutes</default>
  </input>
 </fieldset>

 <row>
  <html>
	<center><h1>Splunk for RSA SecurID Appliances</h1></center><br /><br />
	This application was designed to give users usable data surrounding the activity taking place on their RSA SecurID appliances.  This application will work with both the RSA SecurID Appliance 130 and 230 models.  This summary page provides to you a brief overview of some of the activity on your appliances.  You will find in the AppBar three more views -- "User Activity", "Network Activity" and "Event Search".<br /><br />
	<b>User Activity</b>: In this view you will find successful and failed actions triggered by users along with the reasons for each.  Everything is specific to user actions.<br />
	<b>Network Activity</b>: This view includes reports specifically to do with network activity.  There are connection statistics, in/out packet counts, and much more.  Great for troubleshoot network related issues.<br />
	<b>Event Search</b>: This view will allow you to manually search events triggered by users on the appliances.  You can search by appliance, source host, username, action, action result and result reason.<br /><br />
	For more information please refer to the README.txt found in the parent directory for this application or the Splunkbase page.<br />
  </html>
  <table>
   <searchName>All Users</searchName>
   <title>All Users</title>
   <option name="showPager">true</option>
  </table>
 </row>

 <row>
  <chart>
   <searchName>Events Over Time</searchName>
   <title>Events per 5 minutes</title>
   <option name="charting.chart">line</option>
   <option name="charting.primaryAxisTitle.text">Date and Time</option>
  </chart>
  <chart>
   <searchName>Total Failed and Successful Logins</searchName>
   <title>Total Failed/Successful Logins (5min spans)</title>
   <option name="charting.chart">line</option>
   <option name="charting.primaryAxisTitle.text">Date and Time</option>
  </chart>
 </row>

 <row>
  <table>
   <searchName>Top Ten Connecting Hosts</searchName>
   <title>Top Ten Connecting Hosts</title>
   <option name="count">10</option>
   <option name="showPager">false</option>
  </table>
  <chart>
   <searchName>Top Ten Actions</searchName>
   <title>Top Ten Actions</title>
   <option name="charting.chart">bar</option>
  </chart>
 </row>

</form>
