<dashboard theme="light" version="1.1">
  <label>Form Viz</label>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
        <h2>Form Viz</h2>
        <h4>Version: 2.1.0</h4>
        <p>This app renders SPL results as a dynamic form with <b>freetext</b>, <b>dropdown</b>, <b>radio</b>, <b>checkbox</b>, <b>number</b>, <b>date</b>, <b>spl</b>, <b>description</b>, <b>markdown</b>, and <b>spl_display</b> rows. Responses are saved to a global KV Store collection and tagged with <b>form_name</b> for filtering.</p>
      </html>
    </panel>
  </row>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <viz type="form_viz.form_viz">
        <title>Form Viz - v2.1.0</title>
        <search>
          <query>| inputlookup form_config</query>
          <earliest>-24h@h</earliest>
          <latest>now</latest>
        </search>
        <option name="drilldown">none</option>
        <option name="height">600</option>
        <option name="refresh.display">progressbar</option>
      </viz>
    </panel>
  </row>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
        <h1>How It Works</h1>
        <p>Run SPL that returns these columns:</p>
        <ul>
          <li><b>question</b> (required): label shown above the form field</li>
          <li><b>type</b> (required): <code>freetext</code>, <code>dropdown</code>, <code>radio</code>, <code>checkbox</code>, <code>number</code>, <code>date</code>, <code>spl</code> (multi-line SPL input with a Format button), <code>description</code>, <code>markdown</code>, or <code>spl_display</code> (read-only auto-formatted SPL)</li>
          <li><b>options</b>: comma-separated choices for dropdown/radio/checkbox; description body text for description rows; the SPL string to render for spl_display rows</li>
          <li><b>order</b> (optional): numeric sort order for rendered fields</li>
          <li><b>description</b> (optional): markdown helper text shown under the question label and above the input (the <code>description_above</code> column is still accepted as a backward-compatible alias)</li>
        </ul>

        <h1>Format Options</h1>
        <ul>
          <li><b>Form Name</b> and <b>Output Lookup</b> set the KV Store destination metadata</li>
          <li><b>Display Orders</b> optionally renders only selected order numbers/ranges, for example <code>1,2,3</code>, <code>1-5</code>, or <code>5-9</code></li>
          <li><b>Form Name Token</b> (default <code>form_name</code>)</li>
          <li><b>Output Lookup Token</b> (default <code>form_output_lookup</code>)</li>
        </ul>

        <h1>Ordering</h1>
        <ul>
          <li>If <code>order</code> exists and is numeric, fields are sorted ascending by <code>order</code></li>
          <li>Ties keep original SPL row order</li>
          <li>Rows without numeric <code>order</code> render after ordered rows</li>
          <li>When <b>Display Orders</b> is set, rows outside that filter and rows without numeric order are hidden from that panel</li>
        </ul>

        <h1>Tokens</h1>
        <ul>
          <li><b>$$form_response$$</b>: JSON of answers plus <code>_form_name</code> and <code>_form_output_lookup</code></li>
          <li><b>$$form_name$$</b> and <b>$$form_output_lookup$$</b> (token names configurable)</li>
        </ul>

        <h1>Submission IDs</h1>
        <p>Every answered question from one Submit shares the same <code>submission_id</code>. It is generated in the browser when the user clicks <b>Submit Form</b>:</p>
        <pre>&lt;milliseconds-since-epoch&gt;-&lt;form-name&gt;-&lt;order-scope&gt;-&lt;splunk-user-or-anon&gt;</pre>
        <p>The timestamp uses browser <code>Date.getTime()</code>. The form portion is the resolved form name. The order scope is the <b>Display Orders</b> value with spaces removed when a display filter is set; otherwise it is the sorted answered question orders joined with <code>_</code>, or <code>noorder</code> when answered rows do not have numeric order values. The user portion uses <code>$$env:user$$</code> when Capture User is enabled, otherwise <code>anon</code>. Text parts are normalized to lowercase safe characters. Use it to group one submission batch; each KV Store row still has its own <code>_key</code>.</p>

        <h1>Issues and Limitations</h1>
        <ul>
          <li>For dynamic <code>outputlookup</code> updates of CSV lookups, keep the visualization and lookup in the same app context. Cross-app outputlookup can create app-local shadow lookup files.</li>
          <li>If duplicate question labels are used, token payload keys can collide.</li>
        </ul>

        <h1>Release Notes</h1>
        <h2>v2.1.0</h2>
        <ul>
          <li>Added <b>Display Orders</b> panel setting for rendering selected order numbers/ranges from a larger form definition</li>
          <li><code>submission_id</code> now uses <code>&lt;epoch-ms&gt;-&lt;form-name&gt;-&lt;order-scope&gt;-&lt;user&gt;</code></li>
          <li>Submitted records include the question order whenever the answered row has one</li>
        </ul>
      </html>
    </panel>
  </row>
</dashboard>
